<DOC> <DOCNO> 0 </DOCNO> Coronavirus vaccine: India begins world's biggest drive - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1 </DOCNO> Capitol riots: Who broke into the building? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 2 </DOCNO> Fighting for the Parthenon marbles - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 3 </DOCNO> India coronavirus: How do you vaccinate a billion people? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 4 </DOCNO> Science & Environment - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 5 </DOCNO> Covid-19: France begins 6pm curfew - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 6 </DOCNO> How Saddam Hussein tried to break into the film business - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 7 </DOCNO> UK - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 8 </DOCNO> Honey detective work raises fears for bees - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 9 </DOCNO> Capitol riots: Who broke into the building? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 10 </DOCNO> US Election 2020: What do countries around the world want from Joe Biden? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 11 </DOCNO> World - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 12 </DOCNO> Brexit: GB package to NI had international customs label - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 13 </DOCNO> Indonesia: Archaeologists find world's oldest animal cave painting - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 14 </DOCNO> American Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 15 </DOCNO> Home - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 16 </DOCNO> Two migrant boats intercepted in English Channel - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 17 </DOCNO> Early adventures in snow and cinema - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 18 </DOCNO> UK allows emergency use of bee-harming pesticide - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 19 </DOCNO> Welsh: Learning the language in America and Melbourne - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 20 </DOCNO> BBC Weather </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 21 </DOCNO> Concrete box used as Peterborough railway tunnel in 'UK first' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 22 </DOCNO> Covid-19 vaccines: William 'proud' of Queen and Philip for having jab - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 23 </DOCNO> Home - BBC Reel </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 24 </DOCNO> The 'guerrilla girls' who changed the art world - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 25 </DOCNO> Sutton Hoo: The Anglo Saxon treasures that inspired The Dig starring Ralph Fiennes - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 26 </DOCNO> Gaelic Games - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 27 </DOCNO> World news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 28 </DOCNO> Magicians mark 100 years of 'sawing woman in half' trick - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 29 </DOCNO> Covid: 'Urgent' aviation support plea over travel curbs - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 30 </DOCNO> Australia - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 31 </DOCNO> Trump impeachment: When will he go on trial in the Senate? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 32 </DOCNO> Fake News - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 33 </DOCNO> My trailblazing mother, the world’s first woman prime minister - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 34 </DOCNO> Armin Laschet elected leader of Merkel's CDU party - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 35 </DOCNO> Home - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 36 </DOCNO> Reality Check - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 37 </DOCNO> Coon Cheese rebrands in Australia after anti-racism campaign - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 38 </DOCNO> Lekki toll gate shootings: What really happened? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 39 </DOCNO> Coronavirus vaccine: India begins world's biggest drive - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 40 </DOCNO> Lockdown mental health: Tips for helping your child - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 41 </DOCNO> Business - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 42 </DOCNO> Australia coach Justin Langer defends Tim Paine over sledging criticism - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 43 </DOCNO> US Election 2020 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 44 </DOCNO> Coronavirus - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 45 </DOCNO> Sri Lanka v England: Lahiru Thirimanne leads hosts' fightback in Galle - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 46 </DOCNO> Dr Dre: Rap legend returns home after brain aneurysm - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 47 </DOCNO> Robert Saleh: New York Jets set to appoint first Muslim head coach in NFL - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 48 </DOCNO> Coronavirus vaccines - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 49 </DOCNO> Are women let down by period trackers? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 50 </DOCNO> Tennis stars' arrival angers stranded Australians - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 51 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Further 1,295 deaths recorded in the UK - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 52 </DOCNO> Brexit - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 53 </DOCNO> Family & Education - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 54 </DOCNO> US Capitol riots - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 55 </DOCNO> Music - BBC Culture </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 56 </DOCNO> Newsbeat - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 57 </DOCNO> Bill Belichick: NFL coach turns down Presidential Medal of Freedom - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 58 </DOCNO> Brexit: No plans to dilute workers' rights, minister says - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 59 </DOCNO> Why biopics go so wrong - BBC Culture </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 60 </DOCNO> 2000: The US election decided by the courts - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 61 </DOCNO> Australian Open: Heather Watson among 47 players to quarantine in Melbourne after Covid cases on flights - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 62 </DOCNO> Covid in California: The state is struggling to contain the virus - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 63 </DOCNO> Stories - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 64 </DOCNO> Coronavirus cure: What progress are we making on treatments? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 65 </DOCNO> Australia v India LIVE: Fourth Test, day four commentary & score - Live - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 66 </DOCNO> UK news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 67 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Vaccine patients treated to live organ music while waiting for jab - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 68 </DOCNO> Market Data - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 69 </DOCNO> How can I change my BBC cookie settings? - Using the BBC </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 70 </DOCNO> Consultation launched over gene edited food in England - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 71 </DOCNO> Cycling - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 72 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Africa infections rising sharply in worst-affected countries - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 73 </DOCNO> Insurers must pay many small firms for Covid lockdown losses - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 74 </DOCNO> Coronavirus doctor's diary: Karen caught Covid - and took it home - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 75 </DOCNO> Covid: Australian vaccine abandoned over false HIV response - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 76 </DOCNO> The man startling millions of starlings with lasers - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 77 </DOCNO> Angers 0-1 Paris St-Germain: Layvin Kurzawa strike sends PSG back to the top - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 78 </DOCNO> Nasa's giant SLS rocket: a guide - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 79 </DOCNO> Covid: Cornwall 'faces losing £1bn of visitor spending' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 80 </DOCNO> QAnon: What is it and where did it come from? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 81 </DOCNO> Australia v India: Marnus Labuschagne's century punishes tourists in Brisbane - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 82 </DOCNO> Covaxin: What was the rush to approve India's homegrown vaccine? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 83 </DOCNO> Martin Luther King Jr: New documentary on FBI surveillance - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 84 </DOCNO> Patrick Mahomes: Why Chiefs gave him NFL's biggest deal - Jason Bell Q&A - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 85 </DOCNO> Covid: Car loan lenders can seize vehicles from February - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 86 </DOCNO> Georgia election: Trump voter fraud claims and others fact-checked - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 87 </DOCNO> Covid: How are European countries tackling the pandemic? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 88 </DOCNO> World news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 89 </DOCNO> Coronavirus variants and mutations: The science explained - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 90 </DOCNO> Fulham 0-1 Chelsea: Mason Mount goal settles London derby - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 91 </DOCNO> Australia v India LIVE: Fourth Test, day three commentary & score - Live - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 92 </DOCNO> Joanna Lumley 'shocked' at claims disabled workers unpaid - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 93 </DOCNO> Lockdown: Are people breaking covid rules? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 94 </DOCNO> Australia: Spectacular ‘tree of life’ found in lake - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 95 </DOCNO> How Gambia is grappling with gruesome past under Yahya Jammeh - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 96 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: 'We're Australian but we're trapped in the UK' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 97 </DOCNO> NFL: The Miami Dolphins team of 'misfits' who won the Super Bowl undefeated - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 98 </DOCNO> China - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 99 </DOCNO> Covid-19: More mass jab centres, airport support and a virtual library - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 100 </DOCNO> 'Covid means we may lose our first home' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 101 </DOCNO> Ethiopia's Tigray crisis: Fact-checking misleading images - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 102 </DOCNO> BBC - Homepage </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 103 </DOCNO> Olympics - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 104 </DOCNO> Supermarket staff: 'We're lucky if people wear masks' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 105 </DOCNO> India - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 106 </DOCNO> Brexit: 'Most difficult week I've had in this job in 20 years' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 107 </DOCNO> Ghana election: Fact-checking claims about voting day - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 108 </DOCNO> F1: Australian & Chinese Grands Prix postponed because of coronavirus restrictions - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 109 </DOCNO> China’s pressure and propaganda - the reality of reporting Xinjiang - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 110 </DOCNO> Scottish fishermen 'sailing to Denmark to land catch' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 111 </DOCNO> Did Bournemouth beach crowds spread coronavirus? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 112 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: How India is readying for its massive vaccine drive - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 113 </DOCNO> NFL play-offs super wildcard round: Saints, Browns & Ravens advance - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 114 </DOCNO> Sex and Covid: What are the rules in lockdown? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 115 </DOCNO> UK news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 116 </DOCNO> West Indies in Bangladesh 2021 - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 117 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Three Biden claims about Trump fact-checked - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 118 </DOCNO> Rugby Union - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 119 </DOCNO> Covid: Thanksgiving the cause of a spike in US infections? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 120 </DOCNO> Health - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 121 </DOCNO> Danke Apartment: The 'broken eggshell' that left young Chinese homeless - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 122 </DOCNO> Australia news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 123 </DOCNO> Dustin Higgs: Final execution of Trump presidency is carried out - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 124 </DOCNO> DAX - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 125 </DOCNO> Covid: The truth behind videos of 'empty' hospitals - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 126 </DOCNO> Northern Ireland - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 127 </DOCNO> Why some bike shares work and others don't - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 128 </DOCNO> Morrisons to be first UK supermarket to pay minimum £10 an hour - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 129 </DOCNO> Covid in Wales: GPs warned about delay to vaccine batch - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 130 </DOCNO> Covid: Are lockdown rules changing? Public Health England answers your questions - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 131 </DOCNO> Covid: FDA approves Pfizer vaccine for emergency use in US - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 132 </DOCNO> Why getting a name right matters - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 133 </DOCNO> Kelly Craft: US cancels top envoy's visit to Taiwan - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 134 </DOCNO> Covid vaccine: 'Disappearing' needles and other rumours debunked - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 135 </DOCNO> Science and Environment news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 136 </DOCNO> Australia v India LIVE: Fourth Test, day one commentary & score - Live - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 137 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Call for rethink on lockdown golf ban - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 138 </DOCNO> You Me At Six: Why rock stars don't need to drink - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 139 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Number of Isle of Man active cases rises to 40 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 140 </DOCNO> CAC 40 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 141 </DOCNO> Covid map: Coronavirus cases, deaths, vaccinations by country - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 142 </DOCNO> Brexit: Will the EHIC still be valid and what is the new GHIC card? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 143 </DOCNO> Brexit: Irish hauliers 'bypassing Welsh ports', say bosses - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 144 </DOCNO> Cassette sales double in a year with Lady Gaga best-selling album on tape - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 145 </DOCNO> Covid In Scotland: business clicks but doesn’t collect - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 146 </DOCNO> Covid: Trials to test combination of Oxford and Sputnik vaccines - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 147 </DOCNO> Meng Wanzhou: Bullets sent in mail to Huawei's finance chief - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 148 </DOCNO> Science and Environment news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 149 </DOCNO> One Night In Miami: Muhammad Ali and Jim Brown meeting with Malcolm X depicted in new film - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 150 </DOCNO> Thailand allows visitors to play golf in quarantine - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 151 </DOCNO> Wales - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 152 </DOCNO> Europe's slow start: How many people have had the Covid vaccine? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 153 </DOCNO> Euro (EUR) - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 154 </DOCNO> Brexit shellfish delays leave Scottish seafood rotting - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 155 </DOCNO> India coronavirus: Can its vaccine makers meet demand? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 156 </DOCNO> The other virus that worries Asia - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 157 </DOCNO> Disability Sport - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 158 </DOCNO> Royal Dutch Shell to cut more than 300 North Sea jobs - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 159 </DOCNO> Covid-19 vaccine: 'Others deserve it before me' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 160 </DOCNO> Wiltshire - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 161 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Why are infections rising again in US? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 162 </DOCNO> BBC World News: 24 hour news TV channel - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 163 </DOCNO> Rules of origin: Why are Percy Pigs a headache for M&S? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 164 </DOCNO> Latin America & Caribbean - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 165 </DOCNO> Australia v India LIVE: Fourth Test, day two commentary & score - Live - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 166 </DOCNO> Netball - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 167 </DOCNO> M&S signs call to action over Uighur forced labour - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 168 </DOCNO> Dachaigh - Naidheachdan a' BhBC </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 169 </DOCNO> AEX - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 170 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: India tries new type of tests to tackle virus - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 171 </DOCNO> Woman has nans as bridesmaids after Covid rules hit wedding - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 172 </DOCNO> Covid vaccine: When will you be eligible? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 173 </DOCNO> Media billionaire David Barclay dies, aged 86 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 174 </DOCNO> Swimming - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 175 </DOCNO> Shukatsu sexism: The Japanese jobseekers fighting discrimination - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 176 </DOCNO> Brexit trade deal: What does it mean for fishing? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 177 </DOCNO> NFL Standings - American Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 178 </DOCNO> Covid in Scotland: Mass vaccination of health and care staff begins - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 179 </DOCNO> Customs staff: Vaccinate us to keep trade flowing - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 180 </DOCNO> US & Canada - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 181 </DOCNO> Lockdown 2021: 'It feels like nurseries are an afterthought' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 182 </DOCNO> Waldemar Haffkine: The vaccine pioneer the world forgot - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 183 </DOCNO> Space images: The best of 2020 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 184 </DOCNO> Companies - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 185 </DOCNO> UK economy shrank by 2.6% in November as services suffered - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 186 </DOCNO> Brexit: Five surprising consequences - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 187 </DOCNO> Covid: Nurseries 'teetering on the edge' during pandemic - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 188 </DOCNO> Horse Racing - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 189 </DOCNO> Gold - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 190 </DOCNO> Weather and flood warning as Wales set for three-day rainstorm - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 191 </DOCNO> Capitol riots: How it feels to be an American in the UK - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 192 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Parents with childcare issues 'must get right to furlough' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 193 </DOCNO> Gerry Marsden: Funeral held for Pacemakers star - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 194 </DOCNO> China news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 195 </DOCNO> BBC Sport: Contact, Help & FAQs - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 196 </DOCNO> Georgia election: Donald Trump's phone call fact-checked - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 197 </DOCNO> UK tightens rules on using Uighur-picked cotton - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 198 </DOCNO> Avenue Beat: How do the F2020 singers avoid becoming a one-hit wonder? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 199 </DOCNO> Dr Dre hit with $25m bill for Beats headphones - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 200 </DOCNO> Vikkstar on his plans for growing Call of Duty esports - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 201 </DOCNO> Joe the pigeon spared by Australia after leg tag found to be fake - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 202 </DOCNO> Marine waste turned into beach cleaning equipment - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 203 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Student nurses 'at risk' without insurance on placement - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 204 </DOCNO> Dr Dre removes university boast post about daughter - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 205 </DOCNO> Mount Semeru: Erupting volcano spews ash above Indonesia's Java island - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 206 </DOCNO> Sinovac: Brazil results show Chinese vaccine 50.4% effective - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 207 </DOCNO> Japanese Yen (JPY) - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 208 </DOCNO> Finding Alice: How Keeley Hawes drama offers 'authentic' image of grief - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 209 </DOCNO> US election 2020: Fact-checking Trump team's main fraud claims - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 210 </DOCNO> Tesla asked to recall 158,000 cars over safety concerns - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 211 </DOCNO> Business of Sport - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 212 </DOCNO> NFL predictions: Can Tampa Bay Buccaneers beat New Orleans Saints at third attempt? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 213 </DOCNO> Dr Dre loses trademark battle with a gynaecologist called Dr Drai - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 214 </DOCNO> Crawley's FA Cup hero Nick Tsaroulla's 'dark and difficult time' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 215 </DOCNO> Australia rebukes Google for blocking local content - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 216 </DOCNO> Online clothes sellers targeted by 'creepy' messages - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 217 </DOCNO> Newyddion a mwy - BBC Cymru Fyw </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 218 </DOCNO> Rooney Rule: Does scheme to increase BAME coaching representation actually work? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 219 </DOCNO> Trump's wall: How much has been built during his term? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 220 </DOCNO> Samsung Galaxy S21 Ultra: Does stylus spell end of the Note? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 221 </DOCNO> Senedd: Some Tory candidates 'would scrap' Welsh parliament - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 222 </DOCNO> Afghanistan conflict: Female judges shot dead in Kabul - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 223 </DOCNO> Scotland - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 224 </DOCNO> Dr Dre: Rap legend returns home after brain aneurysm - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 225 </DOCNO> IBEX 35 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 226 </DOCNO> David Attenborough won't return to Instagram - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 227 </DOCNO> Were there hold-ups in first week after Brexit? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 228 </DOCNO> Athletics - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 229 </DOCNO> Covid-19 in the UK: How many coronavirus cases are there in your area? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 230 </DOCNO> Trump's Christian supporters and the march on the Capitol - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 231 </DOCNO> Middle East - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 232 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Why do I need to be tested? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 233 </DOCNO> US election 2020: Can Mike Pence reject Joe Biden's win? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 234 </DOCNO> Cyberpunk 2077: We underestimated difficulties - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 235 </DOCNO> Your Money - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 236 </DOCNO> Gymnastics | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 237 </DOCNO> Newspaper headlines: 'Quarantine hotels' and jab for over-18s 'by June' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 238 </DOCNO> Has coronavirus made us more ethical consumers? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 239 </DOCNO> China: Senior Conservatives call for reset of UK policy - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 240 </DOCNO> One-minute World News - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 241 </DOCNO> Are women let down by period trackers? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 242 </DOCNO> EuroStoxx 50 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 243 </DOCNO> How RuPaul's Drag Race UK faced Covid challenge - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 244 </DOCNO> Cricket - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 245 </DOCNO> Brexit: Welsh seafood in 'grave state' over port delays - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 246 </DOCNO> Get Inspired - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 247 </DOCNO> Air pollution within legal limit 'for first time' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 248 </DOCNO> Femtech: Right time, wrong term? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 249 </DOCNO> Can I hug my vaccinated dad? And other questions - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 250 </DOCNO> Nepali climbers make history with winter summit of K2 mountain - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 251 </DOCNO> New Tech Economy - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 252 </DOCNO> Covid: How worrying are the UK, South Africa, and Brazil coronavirus variants? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 253 </DOCNO> Australian Open qualifying: Francesca Jones wins, Eugenie Bouchard out - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 254 </DOCNO> Snooker - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 255 </DOCNO> Government defends Cumbria coal mine green light - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 256 </DOCNO> Hang Seng - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 257 </DOCNO> Business news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 258 </DOCNO> Will the Trump corporate backlash make a difference? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 259 </DOCNO> China Covid-19: How state media and censorship took on coronavirus - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 260 </DOCNO> Lockdown: 'Why haven't our BTec exams been cancelled too?' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 261 </DOCNO> Covid: 10 new mass vaccination centres to open in England - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 262 </DOCNO> Golf - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 263 </DOCNO> Australia: Man held after armed raid in search of cat - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 264 </DOCNO> Your Coronavirus Stories - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 265 </DOCNO> rewind </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 266 </DOCNO> Wood wins £88m Chinese refinery expansion deal - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 267 </DOCNO> Covid-19: 22 further virus-related deaths announced in NI - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 268 </DOCNO> India in Australia: Jasprit Bumrah - the story behind the bowling sensation - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 269 </DOCNO> How South African police are tackling pangolin smugglers - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 270 </DOCNO> Technology - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 271 </DOCNO> Astronaut Scott Kelly: How to survive a year in space - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 272 </DOCNO> FTSE 100 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 273 </DOCNO> Capitol riots: What happens on Capitol Hill? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 274 </DOCNO> The angry pop song calling out China's domestic violence problem - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 275 </DOCNO> Home Office 'working to restore' lost police records - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 276 </DOCNO> Sex lives of app users 'shared with Facebook' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 277 </DOCNO> Climate change: Weakened 'ice arches' speed loss of Arctic floes - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 278 </DOCNO> NFL divisional play-off games: Baltimore Ravens and Green Bay Packers advance to Championship games - Live - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 279 </DOCNO> Coronavirus news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 280 </DOCNO> Covid: More laptops for homeschooling children in Wales - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 281 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Further 1,295 deaths recorded in the UK - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 282 </DOCNO> Twenty films to watch in 2021 - BBC Culture </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 283 </DOCNO> NASDAQ - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 284 </DOCNO> Australian Open: Andy Murray tests positive for coronavirus - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 285 </DOCNO> Electric eels work together to zap prey - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 286 </DOCNO> Entertainment & Arts - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 287 </DOCNO> US Election 2020: The 'dead voters' in Michigan who are still alive - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 288 </DOCNO> Darts | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 289 </DOCNO> Why self-compassion – not self-esteem – leads to success - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 290 </DOCNO> Biden inauguration: All 50 US states on alert for armed protests - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 291 </DOCNO> Scotland's papers: Vaccine conspiracies and Army helps deliver jabs - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 292 </DOCNO> Are you an NFL rookie? Watch our guide to all things American Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 293 </DOCNO> Chadwick Boseman: A film icon who changed Hollywood - BBC Culture </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 294 </DOCNO> Lockdown Learning: BBC puts school materials on TV, iPlayer and online - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 295 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Protect us from unlawful killing charges - medics - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 296 </DOCNO> China news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 297 </DOCNO> BSE Sensex - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 298 </DOCNO> Australia to kill US pigeon that crossed Pacific - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 299 </DOCNO> Africa internet: Where and how are governments blocking it? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 300 </DOCNO> Covid: 'Chickens can't be furloughed,' egg farm warns - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 301 </DOCNO> Parliaments - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 302 </DOCNO> Local News - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 303 </DOCNO> NFL Scores - NFL Results - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 304 </DOCNO> Rap against Dictatorship: The rappers taking on Thailand's leaders - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 305 </DOCNO> Why Hollywood gets the Irish so wrong - BBC Culture </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 306 </DOCNO> Virtual library gives children in England free book access - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 307 </DOCNO> Covid: What do we know about China's coronavirus vaccines? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 308 </DOCNO> ICYMI: Spacing out and a famous frozen waterfall - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 309 </DOCNO> Evaristo de Macedo: The record-breaking Brazilian loved by Barca & Madrid - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 310 </DOCNO> Climate change: 'Exceptionally hot' 2020 concludes warmest decade - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 311 </DOCNO> Steve Smith 'shocked and disappointed' at claims he erased guard in third Australia-India Test - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 312 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Lewis Hamilton deletes vaccine conspiracy theory post - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 313 </DOCNO> Global Car Industry - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 314 </DOCNO> Notifications, Live Guide, MySport and social media with BBC Sport - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 315 </DOCNO> Man taken to hospital after serious assault in Cardiff - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 316 </DOCNO> Reality Check news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 317 </DOCNO> Astronomy: 'Odd radio circles' in the sky a ‘genuine mystery’ - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 318 </DOCNO> Indonesia earthquake: Dozens dead as search for survivors continues - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 319 </DOCNO> New York transit workers: 'We don't get respect' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 320 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: How will the world vaccinate seven billion? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 321 </DOCNO> England - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 322 </DOCNO> The Instagrammers who worry Iran - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 323 </DOCNO> Covid in Scotland: Where are the latest cases? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 324 </DOCNO> Huawei patent mentions use of Uighur-spotting tech - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 325 </DOCNO> Amazon's Jeff Bezos: The richest person in the world - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 326 </DOCNO> Vaccine rumours debunked: Microchips, 'altered DNA' and more - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 327 </DOCNO> Super Bowl 55: How to follow the 2020-2021 NFL play-offs on the BBC - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 328 </DOCNO> Statues to get protection from 'baying mobs' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 329 </DOCNO> Australia news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 330 </DOCNO> Film - BBC Culture </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 331 </DOCNO> European Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 332 </DOCNO> RAF veteran receives Covid jab at Salisbury Cathedral - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 333 </DOCNO> Nasa's Curiosity rover: 3,000 days on Mars - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 334 </DOCNO> Covid vaccine: How does a vaccine get approved? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 335 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: What has Covid done for climate crisis? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 336 </DOCNO> Health news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 337 </DOCNO> Bitcoin: Newport man's plea to find £210m hard drive in tip - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 338 </DOCNO> Mixed Martial Arts - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 339 </DOCNO> Supermodel Halima Aden: ‘Why I quit’ - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 340 </DOCNO> Coronavirus doctor's diary: ‘Close to death from Covid, I asked them to save my baby’ - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 341 </DOCNO> Covid: Church of England services hit by pandemic - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 342 </DOCNO> Ocean pollutants 'have negative effect on male fertility' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 343 </DOCNO> European - Scores & Fixtures - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 344 </DOCNO> Home - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 345 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Why are we looking at the 'R number' in Wales? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 346 </DOCNO> Scotland - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 347 </DOCNO> Coronavirus news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 348 </DOCNO> Uganda's long-time leader Yoweri Museveni declared election winner - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 349 </DOCNO> ‘My husband’s ashes are still unscattered, but we're doing OK’ - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 350 </DOCNO> New Economy - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 351 </DOCNO> India's top court puts controversial farm laws on hold - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 352 </DOCNO> James Webb will be the 'launch to watch in 2021' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 353 </DOCNO> To poll or not to poll? That is still the question - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 354 </DOCNO> Marseille | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 355 </DOCNO> Covid: Large trial of new treatment begins in UK - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 356 </DOCNO> South East Wales - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 357 </DOCNO> England - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 358 </DOCNO> Covid: Australian Open players frustrated by hotel isolation - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 359 </DOCNO> India's Kumbh Mela festival begins amid Covid concerns - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 360 </DOCNO> Scotland's woodland bird numbers recover after Beast from the East - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 361 </DOCNO> Bordeaux | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 362 </DOCNO> What’s happening to the EU vaccine scheme? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 363 </DOCNO> Business news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 364 </DOCNO> WhatsApp users flock to rival message platforms - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 365 </DOCNO> Global education - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 366 </DOCNO> Rajini Chandy: The 69-year-old Indian actress trolled for ‘too sexy’ photos - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 367 </DOCNO> Liverpool - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 368 </DOCNO> Wylfa: New hybrid nuclear power plan for Anglesey - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 369 </DOCNO> Bombay Jungle: How British Asians broke into London's club scene - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 370 </DOCNO> Paris Saint Germain | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 371 </DOCNO> Capitol riots: What are far-right Trump supporters saying? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 372 </DOCNO> G7: UK to host Cornwall seaside summit in summer - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 373 </DOCNO> NFL play-offs: Drew Brees 'envisioned' Tom Brady clash in divisional round - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 374 </DOCNO> Step-by-step guide to making your own face mask - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 375 </DOCNO> Australia coach Justin Langer defends batsman Steve Smith over scuffing claims - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 376 </DOCNO> Joe Biden unveils $1.9tn US economic relief package - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 377 </DOCNO> Green Bay Packers beat Los Angeles Rams; Buffalo Bills overcome Baltimore Ravens - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 378 </DOCNO> South West Wales - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 379 </DOCNO> Formula 1 - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 380 </DOCNO> Covid-19: UAE dropped from UK travel corridor list - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 381 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Calls for anglers in Wales to be able to drive for fishing - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 382 </DOCNO> Northern Ireland - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 383 </DOCNO> UK Politics - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 384 </DOCNO> French Ligue 1 - Scores & Fixtures - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 385 </DOCNO> Wilmington 1898: When white supremacists overthrew a US government - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 386 </DOCNO> Coronavirus - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 387 </DOCNO> Tennis - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 388 </DOCNO> New intensive care unit planned for Oxford's John Radcliffe Hospital - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 389 </DOCNO> Did we see a Christmas coronavirus spike? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 390 </DOCNO> How six brothers - and their lions - terrorised a Libyan town - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 391 </DOCNO> Europa League | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 392 </DOCNO> What is Elon Musk's Starship? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 393 </DOCNO> Indian farmers protests: The UK children supporting their heritage - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 394 </DOCNO> Covid: 2020 saw most excess deaths since World War Two - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 395 </DOCNO> Rugby League - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 396 </DOCNO> Europe - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 397 </DOCNO> Onid yw cyfenwau yn ddifyr ac amrywiol? - BBC Cymru Fyw </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 398 </DOCNO> Super Nintendo World opening delayed by Japan's virus outbreak - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 399 </DOCNO> The state of the climate in 2021 - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 400 </DOCNO> UK industry bids farewell to EU's Galileo system - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 401 </DOCNO> Monaco | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 402 </DOCNO> 'She is beautiful but she is Indian': The student who became a Welsh bard at 19 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 403 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: ICU staff 'exhausted and apprehensive' amid surge - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 404 </DOCNO> Greener planes of the future... or just pretty plans? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 405 </DOCNO> Families 'struggling to pay for funerals' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 406 </DOCNO> A-level and GCSE grades: Call to scrap 'panic-inducing' tests - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 407 </DOCNO> SLS: Nasa's 'megarocket' engine test ends early - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 408 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Virus provides leaps in scientific understanding - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 409 </DOCNO> Economy - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 410 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Fact-checking fake stories in Africa - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 411 </DOCNO> NFL play-offs super wildcard round: Buccaneers, Bills & Rams advance - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 412 </DOCNO> Hindu shrine desecration: Can Pakistan protect its religious minorities? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 413 </DOCNO> Covid: Will mass community testing be offered across Wales? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 414 </DOCNO> Covid: Airport support scheme to open in England - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 415 </DOCNO> Latin America news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 416 </DOCNO> Champions League Table - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 417 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Dutch shocked to be EU vaccination stragglers - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 418 </DOCNO> Post-Brexit customs systems not fit for purpose, say meat exporters - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 419 </DOCNO> Covid across Europe: As UK prepares for new lockdowns, Europe too is struggling - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 420 </DOCNO> Boxing - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 421 </DOCNO> Williams i golli dechrau'r Chwe Gwlad wedi gwaharddiad - BBC Cymru Fyw </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 422 </DOCNO> In pictures: Winter scenes from around the UK - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 423 </DOCNO> Disability - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 424 </DOCNO> Has Thomas Becket's treasured 'little book' been found? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 425 </DOCNO> Mynor Padilla: Killer of anti-mining activist pleads guilty - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 426 </DOCNO> Lyon | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 427 </DOCNO> Asia - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 428 </DOCNO> Covid in Wales: How many deaths have there been? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 429 </DOCNO> Brexit will increase food supply chain costs, warn business groups - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 430 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Lockdown could 'lose a generation' of young people - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 431 </DOCNO> YesCymru: 'Dim newid ym Mae Caerdydd, dim annibyniaeth' - BBC Cymru Fyw </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 432 </DOCNO> Climate change: US emissions in 2020 in biggest fall since WWII - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 433 </DOCNO> Arrests at Birmingham anti-lockdown protest - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 434 </DOCNO> Was I wrong to fall for a cheating cat? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 435 </DOCNO> WhatsApp extends 'confusing' update deadline - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 436 </DOCNO> French Ligue 1 Table - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 437 </DOCNO> India news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 438 </DOCNO> RSS Feed (Really Simple Syndication) - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 439 </DOCNO> NBA: Kevin Durant and debutant James Harden star in Brooklyn Nets win - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 440 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Brazil hospitals 'run out of oxygen' for virus patients - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 441 </DOCNO> Lockdown Christmas hits: Lidl pink prosecco and takeaways - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 442 </DOCNO> Talia Dean: 'My back pain was misdiagnosed for 15 years - now I can't dance' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 443 </DOCNO> Smart locks: Convenience comes with security doubts - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 444 </DOCNO> As it happened: Not the time for slightest relaxation, PM says - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 445 </DOCNO> Nice | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 446 </DOCNO> Antarctic base opens briefly as berg watch continues - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 447 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Intensive care and other key terms explained - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 448 </DOCNO> Mid Wales - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 449 </DOCNO> Motorsport - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 450 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: William and Kate hear from emergency workers - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 451 </DOCNO> John Lewis suspends click and collect due to virus safety - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 452 </DOCNO> Champions League | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 453 </DOCNO> India coronavirus: The tragedy of the tuk-tuk driver who fled Covid - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 454 </DOCNO> Covid symptoms: What are they and how do I protect myself? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 455 </DOCNO> Newcastle, County Down: Community orchard that will soon bear fruit - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 456 </DOCNO> Long Reads - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 457 </DOCNO> Covid lockdowns prompt fears over child obesity rise - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 458 </DOCNO> Wales - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 459 </DOCNO> Latin America news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 460 </DOCNO> Brexit export EU costs a 'nasty shock' for small business owners - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 461 </DOCNO> Companies news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 462 </DOCNO> Lille | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 463 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Here's how you can stop bad information from going viral - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 464 </DOCNO> 1,000 lost on one boat - this woman hopes to name them - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 465 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Critical care wards are full in hospitals across England - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 466 </DOCNO> Protecting fragile ecosystems from lithium mining - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 467 </DOCNO> Edinburgh Woollen Mill rescue deal to save 2,000 jobs - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 468 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Traders hope shoppers return for Christmas after lockdown - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 469 </DOCNO> NFL play-offs: Chiefs and Packers top seeds on road to Super Bowl 55 - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 470 </DOCNO> Covid: Record deaths in Germany and Russia - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 471 </DOCNO> FinCEN Files: Roman Abramovich had secret stakes in rival players - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 472 </DOCNO> 'Why I quit my job after my home burned down' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 473 </DOCNO> Entrepreneurship - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 474 </DOCNO> Australia v India: Tim Paine says Steve Smith will 'feed' off criticism - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 475 </DOCNO> Uruguay registers record number of new Covid cases - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 476 </DOCNO> Has Scotland been slower to vaccinate over-80s? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 477 </DOCNO> Saint-Étienne | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 478 </DOCNO> Tesco: Brexit disruption 'is a challenge not a crisis' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 479 </DOCNO> Wales news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 480 </DOCNO> 'I made £1,265 selling my clothes second-hand' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 481 </DOCNO> Sports A-Z - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 482 </DOCNO> Ford ends decades of Brazil manufacturing - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 483 </DOCNO> Autism: 'They said bleach would cure my daughter' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 484 </DOCNO> In Pictures - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 485 </DOCNO> Covid: Can my boss force me to go to work? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 486 </DOCNO> Rennes | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 487 </DOCNO> India news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 488 </DOCNO> OnlyFans: Digital footprint concern raised over images - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 489 </DOCNO> Winter Sports - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 490 </DOCNO> Cyclone Imogen: Downgraded storm brings flood warnings to Queensland - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 491 </DOCNO> Covid vaccine: When, where and how will I get my jab? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 492 </DOCNO> Euro 2020: Wales fans face tickets dilemma over potential Covid-19 changes - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 493 </DOCNO> US Dollar (USD) - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 494 </DOCNO> Online clothes sellers targeted by 'creepy' messages - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 495 </DOCNO> Iran internet 'disrupted' ahead of protests - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 496 </DOCNO> Worker quit Lunar Automotive over furlough payments 'nightmare' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 497 </DOCNO> Covid vaccine: Gwynedd pharmacy 'first in Wales to offer jab' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 498 </DOCNO> The teenage Scot who plays the young Wonder Woman - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 499 </DOCNO> Trump takes final swipes at China's big companies - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 500 </DOCNO> Japan 'glasses ban' for women at work sparks backlash - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 501 </DOCNO> Sri Lanka v England: Michael Vaughan says hosts exposed tourists' weaknesses - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 502 </DOCNO> Nikkei 225 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 503 </DOCNO> Premier League - Scores & Fixtures - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 504 </DOCNO> Covid: What's the science when it comes to schools? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 505 </DOCNO> The rollercoaster ride of Scotland's first gold mine - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 506 </DOCNO> Tayside and Central Scotland - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 507 </DOCNO> Deiseb yn galw am adael i bobl deithio er mwyn pysgota - BBC Cymru Fyw </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 508 </DOCNO> Premier League Table - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 509 </DOCNO> Goldman Sachs relaxes dress code for all employees - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 510 </DOCNO> Technology of Business - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 511 </DOCNO> Australia v India: Rohit Sharma wicket leaves hosts on top - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 512 </DOCNO> Zoom launches paid-for live events with OnZoom - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 513 </DOCNO> FTSE 250 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 514 </DOCNO> Covid in Scotland: Parents' verdicts on week one of home-schooling - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 515 </DOCNO> Max Watters: Cardiff City sign Crawley Town striker - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 516 </DOCNO> Indonesia coronavirus: The vaccination drive targeting younger people - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 517 </DOCNO> Australian surfer Mikey Wright rescues woman from Hawaii waves - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 518 </DOCNO> 'Creepy men' message women on Scrabble Go app - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 519 </DOCNO> Iran judiciary may halt protesters' executions after social media storm - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 520 </DOCNO> Basketball - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 521 </DOCNO> Tesla moves a step closer to launching in India - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 522 </DOCNO> How clean is the air in your office? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 523 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Parents' joy as free childcare resumes - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 524 </DOCNO> Wolves 2-3 West Brom: Matheus Pereira's double secures Baggies win in Black Country derby - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 525 </DOCNO> Pound Sterling (GBP) - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 526 </DOCNO> Covid: Jonathan Van-Tam answers your questions on Zoom - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 527 </DOCNO> Shukatsu sexism: The Japanese jobseekers fighting discrimination - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 528 </DOCNO> Al-Qaeda: Pompeo says Iran is jihadist network's 'new home base' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 529 </DOCNO> British Gas staff start five-day strike in 'fire and rehire' row - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 530 </DOCNO> Covid in Scotland: How a pilot ended up producing PPE - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 531 </DOCNO> Premier League Top Scorers - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 532 </DOCNO> Sri Lanka v England LIVE, first Test day four, Galle - score, commentary & updates - Live - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 533 </DOCNO> Health news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 534 </DOCNO> Covid: What happens in a hospital intensive care unit? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 535 </DOCNO> US blacklisting of Houthis 'could tip Yemen into huge famine' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 536 </DOCNO> Cardiff City target right-back signing after Jordi Osei-Tutu setback - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 537 </DOCNO> 'The fake reporter wanted to know about our software' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 538 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Romance scams, the Yahoo boys and my friend Beth - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 539 </DOCNO> Premier League - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 540 </DOCNO> Scottish Premiership: Rate the players in Saturday's matches - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 541 </DOCNO> How Narendra Modi misread the mood of India's angry farmers - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 542 </DOCNO> Covid: 'This is the biggest challenge we've ever seen' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 543 </DOCNO> Why this female garbage truck driver hopes more women will join her - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 544 </DOCNO> Africa - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 545 </DOCNO> Bird charity warns of harm from new wind farm - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 546 </DOCNO> Project 17: One girl's quest for clean water in Rwanda - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 547 </DOCNO> Japan’s labour minister says high heels at work are 'necessary' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 548 </DOCNO> Dundee v Ayr United: Postponement 'farcical' says James McPake - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 549 </DOCNO> Natural gas - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 550 </DOCNO> Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 551 </DOCNO> Home - BBC Culture </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 552 </DOCNO> Giant koala sand art captures Australian bushfires emotions - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 553 </DOCNO> North West Wales - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 554 </DOCNO> Energy bills: Automatic switching plan for fairer tariffs - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 555 </DOCNO> Hundreds of volunteers are helping to map the Great Barrier Reef - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 556 </DOCNO> Cyber-flashing: 'I froze when penis picture dropped on to my phone' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 557 </DOCNO> Covid priority list: When will I get the Covid vaccine? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 558 </DOCNO> Lockerbie: Two routes to justice, no end in sight - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 559 </DOCNO> Dr. Dre - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 560 </DOCNO> England in Sri Lanka 2021: Fixtures, results, scorecards & reports - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 561 </DOCNO> Palm cockatoo: Why a unique ‘drumming’ bird is in peril - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 562 </DOCNO> Oil - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 563 </DOCNO> The five major challenges facing electric vehicles - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 564 </DOCNO> Australia v India: Shardul Thakur and Washington Sundar lead fightback in Brisbane - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 565 </DOCNO> Capitol riots: Who has the FBI arrested so far? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 566 </DOCNO> Police investigate 'first cyber-flashing' case - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 567 </DOCNO> Byron Bay: Why a famous Australian beach is disappearing - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 568 </DOCNO> Future Planet - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 569 </DOCNO> Covid: Benidorm actor Asa Elliot takes supermarket delivery job - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 570 </DOCNO> Morriston Hospital to be powered by solar farm - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 571 </DOCNO> Steelers: How anti-gay row inspired rugby film - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 572 </DOCNO> Streets of Beijing back to life after Covid - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 573 </DOCNO> Covid in Scotland: The six new lockdown rules - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 574 </DOCNO> UK business 'must wake up' to China's Uighur cotton slaves - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 575 </DOCNO> Australian night sky on show in 'starlapse' video - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 576 </DOCNO> Australia v India: Tim Paine v Ravichandran Ashwin - when sledging backfires - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 577 </DOCNO> Barnsley 0-2 Swansea City: Swans move clear of Bournemouth - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 578 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Student union calls for help over private rent - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 579 </DOCNO> US and Canada news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 580 </DOCNO> Afghanistan: Kabul deputy governor killed in 'sticky bomb' attack on car - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 581 </DOCNO> The new 'gold rush' for green lithium - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 582 </DOCNO> North Korea unveils new submarine-launched missile - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 583 </DOCNO> Mother and sisters 'heartbroken' over missing Fenwick man - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 584 </DOCNO> Sylvain Sylvain: New York Dolls guitarist dies aged 69 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 585 </DOCNO> Energy news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 586 </DOCNO> Green sea turtles: Vulnerable animal's hatching season draws to close - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 587 </DOCNO> Afghanistan conflict: Female judges shot dead in Kabul - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 588 </DOCNO> Sri Lanka v England: How to follow tour on the BBC - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 589 </DOCNO> Newport County 0-0 Salford City - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 590 </DOCNO> The great bicycle boom of 2020 </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 591 </DOCNO> China’s pressure and propaganda - the reality of reporting Xinjiang - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 592 </DOCNO> US and Canada news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 593 </DOCNO> 'Yes, people have Zoom fatigue but it's not our fault' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 594 </DOCNO> Scores & Fixtures - Cricket - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 595 </DOCNO> Avenue Beat: How do the F2020 singers avoid becoming a one-hit wonder? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 596 </DOCNO> Afghanistan: Blast kills 15 children in eastern province - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 597 </DOCNO> Douglas Fraser | BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 598 </DOCNO> Face masks: How to wear one correctly - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 599 </DOCNO> Wales politics - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 600 </DOCNO> Entertainment & Arts news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 601 </DOCNO> The assassination of a ‘Brave Journalist of Afghanistan’ - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 602 </DOCNO> How cities are clamping down on cars - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 603 </DOCNO> Climate change: Africa's green energy transition 'unlikely' this decade - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 604 </DOCNO> Capitol riots: Police describe a 'medieval battle' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 605 </DOCNO> Sri Lanka v England: Dan Lawrence - son of a groundsman, brother of a wrestler - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 606 </DOCNO> Climate Basics: CO2 explained - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 607 </DOCNO> Covid-19: New treatment, NHS staff struggles and free meals row - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 608 </DOCNO> China Uighurs: A model's video gives a rare glimpse inside internment - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 609 </DOCNO> North East Wales - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 610 </DOCNO> Lowther Hills wind farm project rejected by government - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 611 </DOCNO> We Are All Birds of Uganda: Will Gompertz reviews Hafsa Zayyan's debut novel ★★★☆☆ - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 612 </DOCNO> Scotland news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 613 </DOCNO> Trump impeachment: Republicans clash as Senate trial looms - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 614 </DOCNO> The futuristic cargo ship made of wood - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 615 </DOCNO> Covid: WHO team probing origin of virus arrives in China - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 616 </DOCNO> Teams - Cricket - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 617 </DOCNO> Your coronavirus stories stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 618 </DOCNO> Why Covid could remove barriers for women in the car industry - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 619 </DOCNO> WandaVision: Critics welcome 'delightful' Disney+ series - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 620 </DOCNO> The inventor inspired by wanting to keep his daughter safe - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 621 </DOCNO> Afghan attack: Babies killed as gunmen storm Kabul maternity ward - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 622 </DOCNO> Biden Twitter account 'starts from zero' with no Trump followers - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 623 </DOCNO> Mount Semeru: Erupting volcano spews ash above Indonesia's Java island - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 624 </DOCNO> Uncle Roger comedian deletes video with China critic - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 625 </DOCNO> Why and how does Future Planet count carbon? - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 626 </DOCNO> Archie Lyndhurst: CBBC star died in his sleep, says mother - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 627 </DOCNO> Davos 2020: Can Formula 1 really go 'carbon neutral' by 2030? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 628 </DOCNO> Australia v India: Will Pucovski's journey to 62 on Test debut - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 629 </DOCNO> 'A Hinge date saved my life' and other cancer dating stories - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 630 </DOCNO> Ring of Fire's volcanic and quake activity is normal, say scientists - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 631 </DOCNO> Covid: UK variant could drive 'rapid growth' in US cases, CDC warns - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 632 </DOCNO> Afghanistan conflict: Top US general meets Taliban negotiators - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 633 </DOCNO> Scotland news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 634 </DOCNO> Enough renewables to meet 90% Scottish electricity demand - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 635 </DOCNO> Dustin Diamond diagnosed with cancer - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 636 </DOCNO> Wales news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 637 </DOCNO> Why I'm feeling hopeful about the environment in 2021 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 638 </DOCNO> Future Planet - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 639 </DOCNO> Honda's Swindon factory temporarily suspends production - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 640 </DOCNO> Covid in Scotland: New restrictions come into force - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 641 </DOCNO> New UK Shared Prosperity Fund to bypass Holyrood - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 642 </DOCNO> Big Bash League: Sydney Sixers beat Perth Scorchers by seven wickets - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 643 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Pupils' pizza donation leaves Stoke-on-Trent nurses 'in tears' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 644 </DOCNO> What impeachment means for Trump, Biden and America - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 645 </DOCNO> The Scottish postman behind 'Sea Shanty TikTok' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 646 </DOCNO> Frankfurt Motor Show: Love, hate and electric cars - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 647 </DOCNO> People's Energy data breach affects all 270,000 customers - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 648 </DOCNO> The new fuel to come from Saudi Arabia - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 649 </DOCNO> Covid-19: 'Very little' virus risk at nurseries, says vaccine minister - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 650 </DOCNO> White House: The full-sized Oval Office replica in Norfolk - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 651 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: What powers do police have if people break Covid rules? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 652 </DOCNO> Hyundai's confusion over Apple electric car tie-up - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 653 </DOCNO> 'Leonard's Labour leadership just wasn't working' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 654 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Bracknell couple's 'final meeting' in hospital - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 655 </DOCNO> Scotland to suspend travel corridors from Monday - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 656 </DOCNO> US Election 2020: Can you trust the polls? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 657 </DOCNO> Cricket quiz: What can you remember about the international & domestic summer? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 658 </DOCNO> Scotland business - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 659 </DOCNO> How did debut artist Olivia Rodrigo break chart records? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 660 </DOCNO> Bournemouth 0-1 Luton Town: Kiernan Dewsbury-Hall goal sinks 10-man Cherries - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 661 </DOCNO> Cardiff City 1-2 Norwich City: Hanley and Cantwell strike for Championship leaders - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 662 </DOCNO> Quiz: How much do you remember about England v Pakistan Tests? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 663 </DOCNO> Uber sells self-driving cars to focus on profits - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 664 </DOCNO> Energy news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 665 </DOCNO> Reducing brain damage in sport without losing the thrills - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 666 </DOCNO> In Trump’s final days, a rush of federal executions - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 667 </DOCNO> Covid in Scotland: Barra outbreak 'serious and escalating' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 668 </DOCNO> Arbroath recovery seals 2-2 draw with Queen of the South - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 669 </DOCNO> Entertainment & Arts news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 670 </DOCNO> Honda pauses production after UK port woes - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 671 </DOCNO> Why imposter syndrome hits women and women of colour harder - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 672 </DOCNO> Inauguration 2021: What happens on the day Joe Biden and Kamala Harris are sworn in? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 673 </DOCNO> How machine learning is allowing thousands of students to sit exams at home - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 674 </DOCNO> A ride that 'just feels safer' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 675 </DOCNO> Fleetwood Town 0-1 Portsmouth - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 676 </DOCNO> Business of Sport news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 677 </DOCNO> Recordings show lockdown London quieter than 1928 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 678 </DOCNO> China's Baidu and Geely partner up for smart cars - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 679 </DOCNO> UK leading the way in use of language-learning apps - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 680 </DOCNO> What is the starting point for WHO’s Wuhan Covid probe? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 681 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: All Blacks rugby looking at private equity bids - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 682 </DOCNO> South Scotland - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 683 </DOCNO> Cricket quiz: Can you name England's male Twenty20 players? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 684 </DOCNO> London - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 685 </DOCNO> Carillion: Legal bid launched to ban former directors - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 686 </DOCNO> Why 'Dinner Table Syndrome' is getting worse for deaf people - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 687 </DOCNO> Tidal energy: Plans for Mostyn lagoon take step forward - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 688 </DOCNO> India coronavirus doctors: Notes on hope, fear and longing - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 689 </DOCNO> Bristol City 2-0 Preston North End: Diedhiou and Vyner seal points for Robins - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 690 </DOCNO> Trump's Christian supporters and the march on the Capitol - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 691 </DOCNO> Honda to resume UK output after problems at ports - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 692 </DOCNO> Tokyo Olympics postponement leaves UK firms in limbo - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 693 </DOCNO> Green energy: NI's wind turbines generate controversy - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 694 </DOCNO> Sportscene Predictions: Amy Irons v The Pundits - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 695 </DOCNO> Toby Young: Telegraph coronavirus column 'significantly misleading' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 696 </DOCNO> England in Sri Lanka: 'Joe Root shows he has talent of world's best' - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 697 </DOCNO> Luxury carmaker Maybach has high ambitions for China - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 698 </DOCNO> Equality Matters - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 699 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Why many are still shielding... With no end in sight - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 700 </DOCNO> Ole Gunnar Solskjaer: Man Utd back boss as quarterly financial results published early in error - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 701 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Is virtual reality tourism about to take off? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 702 </DOCNO> Covid: Frank Turner livestream gigs for struggling venues return - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 703 </DOCNO> Big Bash League Table - Cricket - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 704 </DOCNO> Tesla: German court halts factory plan over snake and lizard habitats - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 705 </DOCNO> Champion golfer Ángel Cabrera 'arrested in Brazil' over alleged assault - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 706 </DOCNO> 'Money is tight' - Living on Universal Credit in lockdown - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 707 </DOCNO> Would you trust a 'virtual nanny' with your kids? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 708 </DOCNO> Derby County 0-1 Rotherham United: Millers spoil Wayne Rooney's big day - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 709 </DOCNO> Lily Allen opens up about addiction to Adderall for weight loss - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 710 </DOCNO> Manchester - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 711 </DOCNO> Motherwell v Rangers: Name sides from 2002 Steelmen victory - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 712 </DOCNO> Covid Brazilian variant sparks South America travel ban - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 713 </DOCNO> George Floyd death: Trump's church visit shocks religious leaders - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 714 </DOCNO> Iran women dance in support of arrested Instagram teen - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 715 </DOCNO> Business of Sport news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 716 </DOCNO> Covid: Big Fat Gypsy Wedding star Paddy Doherty in hospital - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 717 </DOCNO> A brief history of Topshop: From basement to high-street empire - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 718 </DOCNO> The docility myth flattening Asian women’s careers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 719 </DOCNO> Tech Tent: Is Tesla really worth $500 billion? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 720 </DOCNO> Big Bash League: Adam Zampa takes 5-17 as Melbourne Stars thrash Adelaide Strikers - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 721 </DOCNO> BBC Sound of 2021: Berwyn's breakthrough songs of 'blood, sweat and tears' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 722 </DOCNO> Women - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 723 </DOCNO> Nike turns to digital sales during China shutdown - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 724 </DOCNO> Masters snooker 2021: John Higgins to face Yan Bingtao in final - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 725 </DOCNO> Bournemouth student feels 'forgotten' during the pandemic - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 726 </DOCNO> Code Switching: What is it and why do we all do it? - BBC Reel </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 727 </DOCNO> Which shops are open and what are the rules about click-and-collect? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 728 </DOCNO> UK car industry warns of £55bn no-deal Brexit hit - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 729 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Harlow Council closes playgrounds - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 730 </DOCNO> The Instagrammers who worry Iran - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 731 </DOCNO> Covid: UK's ban on South America and Portugal travellers comes into force - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 732 </DOCNO> What Trump could do after leaving the White House - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 733 </DOCNO> Trump impeachment: President faces Senate trial after historic second charge - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 734 </DOCNO> Highlands & Islands - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 735 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: The realities of schooling in rural Brazil - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 736 </DOCNO> Psychology - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 737 </DOCNO> Iran arrests men for 'selling babies on Instagram' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 738 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: 'We made a feature film in lockdown' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 739 </DOCNO> UK new car registrations in 2020 sink to 30-year low - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 740 </DOCNO> Burnley: Clarets subject of Â£200m takeover bid by Mohamed El Kashashy & Chris Farnell - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 741 </DOCNO> Twitter 'permanently suspends' Trump's account - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 742 </DOCNO> White Bengal tiger cub born at Nicaragua zoo - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 743 </DOCNO> Covid in Scotland: When will I be vaccinated against the virus? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 744 </DOCNO> Diversity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 745 </DOCNO> Primark refuses to go online despite £1bn lockdown loss - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 746 </DOCNO> James Anderson & Stuart Broad: Should England duo tour Australia next winter? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 747 </DOCNO> Dinosaurs In Love: Tom Rosenthal and daughter's song made into book - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 748 </DOCNO> Syria war: Suspected Israeli strikes on Iran-linked targets 'kill dozens' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 749 </DOCNO> India Covid-19: Bihar braces for 'coronavirus storm' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 750 </DOCNO> Parler: Amazon to remove site from web hosting service - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 751 </DOCNO> Remote Control - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 752 </DOCNO> Firms told to look out for domestic abuse signs - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 753 </DOCNO> Edinburgh, Fife & East Scotland - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 754 </DOCNO> Covid: What is the Oxford vaccine and how does it work? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 755 </DOCNO> Fiat Chrysler and PSA shareholders approve merger - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 756 </DOCNO> Obituary: Sheldon Adelson, the casino magnate who moved an embassy - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 757 </DOCNO> Coronavirus lockdown: The Indian migrants dying to get home - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 758 </DOCNO> Firms scrap political donations over Capitol riots - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 759 </DOCNO> Cyfarthfa hopes to become king of Wales' castles with £50m upgrade - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 760 </DOCNO> Ryan Reynolds and Rob McElhenney: Hollywood stars to take over Wrexham - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 761 </DOCNO> Cricket quiz: Name every cricketer to play for England in 2020 - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 762 </DOCNO> Edward Colston statue: Four charged with criminal damage - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 763 </DOCNO> How the pandemic could redefine our productivity obsession - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 764 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Brazil travel ban to be discussed over new variant - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 765 </DOCNO> Kuwait's stateless man who set himself alight - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 766 </DOCNO> Do you have a question for BBC News? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 767 </DOCNO> US firms condemn 'appalling' insurrection - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 768 </DOCNO> Companies news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 769 </DOCNO> NE Scotland, Orkney & Shetland - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 770 </DOCNO> Wales business - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 771 </DOCNO> Salvador Cienfuegos: Mexico clears ex-defence minister over US drugs link claims - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 772 </DOCNO> Barcelona: Sponsor to name Nou Camp for coronavirus funds - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 773 </DOCNO> Statues to get protection from 'baying mobs' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 774 </DOCNO> Tesla: Soaring share price creates army of 'Teslanaires' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 775 </DOCNO> Bentley ordered to destroy clothing in fashion line trademark row - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 776 </DOCNO> The four keys that could unlock procrastination - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 777 </DOCNO> New York City is latest to cut Trump business ties - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 778 </DOCNO> 'Meithrinfeydd wrth ymyl y dibyn' yn ystod y pandemig - BBC Cymru Fyw </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 779 </DOCNO> Part of rail bridge collapses near fatal Stonehaven derailment site - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 780 </DOCNO> Algeria: a risky place to be a football coach? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 781 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: How technology could keep football fans safe at stadiums - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 782 </DOCNO> Covid: Third time lucky for kidney transplant siblings - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 783 </DOCNO> Tesla: Elon Musk moves to Texas in Silicon Valley snub - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 784 </DOCNO> Edward Colston statue: Protesters tear down slave trader monument - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 785 </DOCNO> Poshmark turns used clothes into $7.1bn stock listing - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 786 </DOCNO> Quiz: Can you name all of England men's Test players from this century - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 787 </DOCNO> Trump National stripped of 2022 US PGA Championship - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 788 </DOCNO> Beny Steinmetz: Mining tycoon in Swiss trial over Guinea deal - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 789 </DOCNO> Manchester United's revenue falls by nearly 12% - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 790 </DOCNO> Covid in Scotland: The people who have lost their lives to Covid-19 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 791 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: How to stay cool in a face mask as hot UK weather forecast - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 792 </DOCNO> 'I was embarrassed to tell friends about my business' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 793 </DOCNO> Pimlico Plumbers to make workers get vaccinations - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 794 </DOCNO> How to function in times of uncertainty - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 795 </DOCNO> Paris St-Germain: Mauricio Pochettino wins first trophy of managerial career - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 796 </DOCNO> Aberdeen performance 'Not good enough' - Derek McInnes - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 797 </DOCNO> Rugby League World Cup 2021 in England aims for high impact - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 798 </DOCNO> UAE-Ireland ODI in Abu Dhabi postponed for third time despite no new cases - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 799 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: When home is both prison and sanctuary - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 800 </DOCNO> Uighur-identifying patent is 'deeply disturbing' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 801 </DOCNO> Cuba placed back on US terrorism sponsor list - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 802 </DOCNO> German freight giant DB Schenker pauses UK deliveries - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 803 </DOCNO> Kyle Jamieson: The new 6ft 8in star of New Zealand cricket - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 804 </DOCNO> Valencia | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 805 </DOCNO> Churchill statue 'may have to be put in museum', says granddaughter - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 806 </DOCNO> 'Performance had everything' - Ross County manager John Hughes - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 807 </DOCNO> Coronavirus testing - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 808 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Brazil virus already in UK ‘not variant of concern’, scientist says - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 809 </DOCNO> Covid: London surfers turned back from Devon - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 810 </DOCNO> Averages - County Championship - Division One - Cricket - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 811 </DOCNO> Shakira is the latest star to sell the rights to her songs - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 812 </DOCNO> Rugby Football Union: O2 signs new five-year deal with RFU - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 813 </DOCNO> Jen Reid: Bristol Black Lives Matter statue removed - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 814 </DOCNO> Dundee United need to be more clinical, says Micky Mellon - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 815 </DOCNO> Airline industry needs up to another $80bn to survive pandemic - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 816 </DOCNO> Argentines on abortion legalisation: 'I felt relieved' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 817 </DOCNO> Airbnb cancels reservations in Washington area ahead of inauguration - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 818 </DOCNO> Kangaroos can 'communicate' with humans, study finds - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 819 </DOCNO> Apps - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 820 </DOCNO> DJ fined £10,000 over rave attended by 150 people - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 821 </DOCNO> Over-50s rush to book holidays as vaccine boosts confidence - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 822 </DOCNO> County Cricket - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 823 </DOCNO> Covid in Scotland: How do the rules compare to last year? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 824 </DOCNO> Fiorentina 1-2 Inter Milan: Romelu Lukaku scores extra-time winner - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 825 </DOCNO> Who was Edward Colston and why is Bristol divided by his legacy? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 826 </DOCNO> Online schooling: Calls to cut data fees during Covid lockdowns - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 827 </DOCNO> Electric Cars: Is it time to buy one? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 828 </DOCNO> Hampshire rail manager avoids 60mph train by 'a second' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 829 </DOCNO> Manchester United financial statement shows Â£70m drop in expected revenue during pandemic - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 830 </DOCNO> England Cricket Team | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 831 </DOCNO> Premier League Table - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 832 </DOCNO> Spanish La Liga Table - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 833 </DOCNO> WhatsApp changes: Signal messaging platform stops working as downloads surge - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 834 </DOCNO> Will the Trump corporate backlash make a difference? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 835 </DOCNO> How to get a job: Top bosses share their secrets - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 836 </DOCNO> Reading attack: Man held after 'window cleaner' appeal - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 837 </DOCNO> Hamilton unlucky over Covid issues, says Rice after 0-0 draw with Dundee Utd - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 838 </DOCNO> Hunger strike refugee's appeal over age rejected - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 839 </DOCNO> Fortnite-maker Epic Games sues Apple and Google in UK - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 840 </DOCNO> Biden inauguration: All 50 US states on alert for armed protests - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 841 </DOCNO> Newcastle United offer season ticket refunds to fans for behind-closed-doors games - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 842 </DOCNO> Scores & Fixtures - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 843 </DOCNO> Watch: Bayern knocked out of German Cup by second-tier side - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 844 </DOCNO> Poland proposes social media 'free speech' law - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 845 </DOCNO> Have female CEOs coped better with Covid than men? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 846 </DOCNO> Gary Wilson column: Ireland in Abu Dhabi bubble for UAE & Afghanistan series - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 847 </DOCNO> Food parcels 'a welcome gift' for struggling fishermen - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 848 </DOCNO> Egypt court overturns TikTok stars' jail sentences - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 849 </DOCNO> Kayla Mueller's parents: 'We can't let her down again' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 850 </DOCNO> Villarreal | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 851 </DOCNO> Uganda social media ban raises questions over regulation in Africa - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 852 </DOCNO> Silencing Trump: How 'big tech' is taking Trumpism offline - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 853 </DOCNO> Green Bay Packers beat Los Angeles Rams; Buffalo Bills overcome Baltimore Ravens - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 854 </DOCNO> Ross County 4-1 Aberdeen: John Hughes' side hammer visitors - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 855 </DOCNO> EFL calls government position on fans in stadiums 'frustrating and perplexing' - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 856 </DOCNO> Hampshire & Isle of Wight - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 857 </DOCNO> Spanish Super Cup: Barcelona beat Real Sociedad on penalties to reach final - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 858 </DOCNO> Why Africa's animation scene is booming - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 859 </DOCNO> Women's Cricket - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 860 </DOCNO> Dog theft: Organised crime driving ‘epidemic’ of dog snatching - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 861 </DOCNO> Trump supporters planning armed protests ahead of Biden inauguration, FBI warns - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 862 </DOCNO> Saman Ghoddos: Brentford sign forward in permanent deal, while Pontus Jansson has surgery - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 863 </DOCNO> Donald Trump's life story: From hotel developer to president - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 864 </DOCNO> Regions - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 865 </DOCNO> Upcycling sports shirts and aeroplane seats - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 866 </DOCNO> Cristiano Ronaldo: Has the Juventus forward equalled world goalscoring record? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 867 </DOCNO> Should you tip the takeaway delivery driver? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 868 </DOCNO> A night at India's largest farmers' protest - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 869 </DOCNO> Capitol riots: Did Trump's words at rally incite violence? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 870 </DOCNO> St Johnstone 1-0 St Mirren: Goodwin left frustrated with referee in his side's defeat - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 871 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Lebanon to impose round-the-clock curfew as cases spike - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 872 </DOCNO> YouTube suspends Donald Trump's channel - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 873 </DOCNO> Technology news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 874 </DOCNO> Manchester United defender Timothy Fosu-Mensah moves to Bayer Leverkusen - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 875 </DOCNO> New jobs in UK hospitality sector 'non-existent' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 876 </DOCNO> EFL: Wayne Rooney's first day to forget, while Forest and Rochdale entertain - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 877 </DOCNO> FBI busts militia 'plot' to abduct Michigan Gov Gretchen Whitmer - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 878 </DOCNO> Hamilton content with point, says Brian Rice after 0-0 with Dundee United - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 879 </DOCNO> Iraqi interpreters 'stalked by death squads' for helping the British - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 880 </DOCNO> Irish Premiership: Sean O'Neill believes completing 38-game league season will be 'really difficult' - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 881 </DOCNO> Quiz: Can you name all England v West Indies centurions since 1988? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 882 </DOCNO> Elon Musk sent letter asking him to invest in Swindon - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 883 </DOCNO> EFL rejects Premier League's Â£50m rescue package for League One and Two clubs - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 884 </DOCNO> 'It feels so good to be back dancing' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 885 </DOCNO> Are pandemics the new normal? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 886 </DOCNO> Supermodel Halima Aden: ‘Why I quit’ - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 887 </DOCNO> Periods - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 888 </DOCNO> Hibernian 2-0 Kilmarnock: A bump along the road - Millen - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 889 </DOCNO> Londonderry security alert declared an 'elaborate hoax' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 890 </DOCNO> Mauricio Pochettino: Paris St-Germain boss tests positive for Covid-19 - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 891 </DOCNO> Covid: Networks 'should give data to Wales' schoolchildren' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 892 </DOCNO> Covid: UK staycation boom predicted once lockdown lifts - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 893 </DOCNO> The woman pushing GB snowsport towards new heights - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 894 </DOCNO> Covid symptoms: Coronavirus Vs cold which do I have? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 895 </DOCNO> Thai monarchy: Royalists stage show of support for the king - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 896 </DOCNO> Hibernian 2-0 Kilmarnock: We did ugly side of the game well - Jack Ross - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 897 </DOCNO> England in Sri Lanka: 'A hectic year ends in Australia but other Tests matter' - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 898 </DOCNO> Middle East news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 899 </DOCNO> German Bundesliga - Scores & Fixtures - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 900 </DOCNO> England news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 901 </DOCNO> Milk Tea Alliance: Thai and Hong Kong activists on fight for democracy - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 902 </DOCNO> As it happened: New tech unveiled at CES 2021 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 903 </DOCNO> Church pastor exposed as a career con artist - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 904 </DOCNO> Private equity firm eyes stake in All Blacks - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 905 </DOCNO> Glasgow 23-22 Edinburgh: Hosts level 1872 Cup series at 1-1 with Pro14 win - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 906 </DOCNO> Tasmania Berlin: The curious German club keen to remain the Bundesliga's worst - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 907 </DOCNO> World Cup 2022: Northern Ireland's opening qualifier against Italy to be played in Parma - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 908 </DOCNO> Wimborne Militia Facebook accounts deactivated for second time - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 909 </DOCNO> Thai protests: Thousands join rally in Bangkok - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 910 </DOCNO> Covid: Australian Open players frustrated by hotel isolation - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 911 </DOCNO> Bristol Rovers 0-1 Charlton Athletic - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 912 </DOCNO> Your coronavirus stories stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 913 </DOCNO> Middle East news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 914 </DOCNO> Singapore firm pushes ahead with Newcastle United bid - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 915 </DOCNO> Celtic 0-0 Livingston: Makeshift Celtic held at home - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 916 </DOCNO> K2: 'Savage Mountain' beckons for unprecedented winter climb - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 917 </DOCNO> Real Madrid | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 918 </DOCNO> Thailand’s youth rebellion: Protest movement demands monarchy reform - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 919 </DOCNO> Wilmington 1898: When white supremacists overthrew a US government - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 920 </DOCNO> G7 summit 'fantastic opportunity' for Cornwall - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 921 </DOCNO> Technology news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 922 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: The hidden heroes of India’s Covid-19 wards - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 923 </DOCNO> Nike's diversity advert causing a backlash in Japan - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 924 </DOCNO> Nepali climbers make history with winter summit of K2 mountain - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 925 </DOCNO> Real Betis | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 926 </DOCNO> Brexit trade talks with India: 'We don't duck the difficult issues' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 927 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Three fined for 50-mile burger trip to Dublin - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 928 </DOCNO> Maradona: Why the football icon's inheritance could be messy - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 929 </DOCNO> Google tries to allay Fitbit-deal privacy fears - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 930 </DOCNO> Hibernian 2-0 Kilmarnock: Jack Ross says playing 'ugly' lifted side into third - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 931 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: What questions do you have? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 932 </DOCNO> Covid: What are the lockdown rules across the UK? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 933 </DOCNO> Bury: Bringing Football Back - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 934 </DOCNO> Adidas considers selling off its Reebok brand - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 935 </DOCNO> Clashes between police and protesters in Bangkok - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 936 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Dr Radha's five mental health tips for lockdown - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 937 </DOCNO> Covid-19: BT extends free wi-fi voucher codes to NI pupils - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 938 </DOCNO> Uganda elections 2021: What you need to know - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 939 </DOCNO> Evaristo de Macedo: The record-breaking Brazilian loved by Barca & Madrid - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 940 </DOCNO> Covid exercise: 'I'll never go back to the gym again' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 941 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Ambulance and police staff open up to royals about bereavement on the frontline - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 942 </DOCNO> Mauricio Pochettino is back - but why has he chosen Paris St-Germain? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 943 </DOCNO> Melton Mowbray swimmer completes ice bath challenge - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 944 </DOCNO> Covid: Couple fined for seven-mile trip to care home - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 945 </DOCNO> Covid lockdown: tougher rules in shops in Wales - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 946 </DOCNO> Euro 2020 finals games at Hampden should go ahead 'with crowd of sorts' - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 947 </DOCNO> Athletic Bilbao | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 948 </DOCNO> England's children decline 'significantly' in science tests - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 949 </DOCNO> Tees - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 950 </DOCNO> Covid-19: NI economy expected to stall after record growth - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 951 </DOCNO> Newtownbutler: Police aware of dissidents' aircraft attack claim - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 952 </DOCNO> Climate Check - BBC Weather </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 953 </DOCNO> Boris Johnson gets angry about girls' education - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 954 </DOCNO> Travel abroad UK: how to fly during a Covid pandemic - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 955 </DOCNO> Atletico Madrid 2-0 Sevilla: Diego Simeone's side extend La Liga lead - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 956 </DOCNO> How to share your questions, stories, pictures and videos with BBC News - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 957 </DOCNO> Scotland politics - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 958 </DOCNO> Belfast Multi-Cultural Association fire 'was deliberate hate crime' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 959 </DOCNO> Fee support extended for EU students - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 960 </DOCNO> Uganda's long-time leader Yoweri Museveni declared election winner - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 961 </DOCNO> Cornwall 'hot rocks' firm claims breakthrough deal - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 962 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Funding for taxi drivers ineligible for first grant - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 963 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Men fined for not wearing face masks in Aldi - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 964 </DOCNO> TikTok level crossing stunt 'staggeringly stupid' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 965 </DOCNO> Ethiopia Tigray crisis: EU concern over war crime reports - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 966 </DOCNO> Global Car Industry news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 967 </DOCNO> Uganda elections 2021: Who is Bobi Wine? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 968 </DOCNO> The film crews being directed from a continent away - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 969 </DOCNO> Northern Ireland news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 970 </DOCNO> Nazi Buchenwald camp no place for sledging, authorities warn - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 971 </DOCNO> Wikipedia at 20: The encyclopedia in five articles - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 972 </DOCNO> Bosman at 25: Who made the best free transfer? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 973 </DOCNO> BBC Have Your Say on WhatsApp - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 974 </DOCNO> Glasgow & West Scotland - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 975 </DOCNO> Extremism is global education fight, says Blair - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 976 </DOCNO> What is GDP and how is it measured? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 977 </DOCNO> Uganda election: False claims about Joe Biden and others - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 978 </DOCNO> Brexit leaves Spain's Costa Brits facing dilemmas - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 979 </DOCNO> Cyber criminals demand ransom to unlock Sepa systems - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 980 </DOCNO> Your pictures on the theme of 'autumn landscapes' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 981 </DOCNO> Cornwall - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 982 </DOCNO> Covid contraction shrinks German economy by 5% - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 983 </DOCNO> NI 100 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 984 </DOCNO> Farming: ‘Radical’ changes set out in post-Brexit plan - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 985 </DOCNO> Michael D Higgins: Mother-and-baby homes a 'violation of rights' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 986 </DOCNO> Champions League: Which goalscorer are you? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 987 </DOCNO> Watford man who tried to buy grenades on dark web sentenced - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 988 </DOCNO> 'I used to hate road cycling, now I design biking gear' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 989 </DOCNO> Africa's week in pictures: 1 - 7 January 2021 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 990 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Universities fear fall in lucrative overseas students - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 991 </DOCNO> Global Car Industry news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 992 </DOCNO> Man has two guesses to unlock bitcoin worth $240m - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 993 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Belfast doctor warns oxygen supplies under 'extreme pressure' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 994 </DOCNO> Covid: Actors give safety training to North Sea wind farm workers - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 995 </DOCNO> US election 2020: How much did it cost and who paid for it? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 996 </DOCNO> Your pictures on the theme of 'monochrome' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 997 </DOCNO> Spurs player in global teacher prize shortlist - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 998 </DOCNO> Spanish Super Cup: Athletic Bilbao to play Barcelona in final after knocking out Real Madrid - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 999 </DOCNO> UK economy 'to get worse before it gets better' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1000 </DOCNO> Uganda elections 2021: How ex-rebel Yoweri Museveni has stayed in power for 35 years - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1001 </DOCNO> England news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1002 </DOCNO> Londonderry: Man injured in 'barbaric shooting' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1003 </DOCNO> Sizewell C: Government in talks to fund £20bn nuclear plant - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1004 </DOCNO> German sports doctor jailed over blood doping scandal - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1005 </DOCNO> Creating animal food from a greenhouse gas - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1006 </DOCNO> PA photographers pick their top shots of 2020 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1007 </DOCNO> Entrepreneurship news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1008 </DOCNO> Covid: Fines after drinkers found in pub 'watching TV with staff' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1009 </DOCNO> Sir Jim Ratcliffe confirms new vehicle to be made in France - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1010 </DOCNO> 'Working from home has made childcare easier' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1011 </DOCNO> Brexit: Dublin Port 'minefield' leaves trucks stranded - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1012 </DOCNO> Villarejo: The rise and fall of the Spanish state's secret fixer - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1013 </DOCNO> Global literacy targets already off track - Unesco - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1014 </DOCNO> Amazon's Panorama box lets firms check if staff follow coronavirus rules - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1015 </DOCNO> Gender - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1016 </DOCNO> Elon Musk's six secrets to business success - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1017 </DOCNO> Porsche set to lead the charge at Frankfurt show - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1018 </DOCNO> SmartDot radiation-protection phone stickers 'have no effect' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1019 </DOCNO> Champions League: Which clubs have made the group stages at least twice? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1020 </DOCNO> Tuam: 'I need to know what happened to my brothers' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1021 </DOCNO> Leicester City 2-0 Southampton: James Maddison and Harvey Barnes send Foxes second - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1022 </DOCNO> Kenyan science teacher Peter Tabichi wins global prize - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1023 </DOCNO> Online shopping - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1024 </DOCNO> Tesla to join key share index as it defies critics - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1025 </DOCNO> 'I monitor my staff with software that takes screenshots' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1026 </DOCNO> Barcelona | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1027 </DOCNO> Economy news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1028 </DOCNO> UK weather: Disruption fears lift as snow moves on from UK - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1029 </DOCNO> How US students get a university degree for free in Germany - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1030 </DOCNO> The boss who bounced her way to £3m from just £200 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1031 </DOCNO> Technology of Business news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1032 </DOCNO> Electric car battery factory to be built in Northumberland - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1033 </DOCNO> Virgin Media broadband price rises of up to £54 in 2021 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1034 </DOCNO> Retail sales in 2020 'worst for 25 years' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1035 </DOCNO> N. Ireland Politics - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1036 </DOCNO> Odion Ighalo: MLS is just one of many options for Nigeria striker - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1037 </DOCNO> Europe news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1038 </DOCNO> Week in pictures: 12-18 December 2020 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1039 </DOCNO> Sesame Street at 50: Five defining moments - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1040 </DOCNO> 'I had zero plans beyond my parents' kitchen' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1041 </DOCNO> Be a 'secret agent' and other new ways to exercise - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1042 </DOCNO> Brexit: Toyota says no-deal outcome will be 'very negative' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1043 </DOCNO> Pupils in Scotland struggle to get online amid Microsoft issue - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1044 </DOCNO> 'Sinister' arson attack on Antrim house investigated - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1045 </DOCNO> Borussia Dortmund: What does Lucien Favre's sacking mean for star players? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1046 </DOCNO> TSB: What does it mean for a town when a bank closes? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1047 </DOCNO> Viewpoint: Global media's Nigeria abductions coverage 'wrong' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1048 </DOCNO> Striking news photos from around the world in 2020 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1049 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: EU anger over delayed Pfizer vaccine deliveries - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1050 </DOCNO> Leeds 0-1 Brighton: Neal Maupay's goal ends Seagulls' winless league run - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1051 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Harvard and MIT sue over US visa ruling - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1052 </DOCNO> 'Someone needs to help parents control their kids' spending' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1053 </DOCNO> West Bromwich Albion | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1054 </DOCNO> Brexit: Republic of Ireland to lose 15% of fishing quota - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1055 </DOCNO> Getafe | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1056 </DOCNO> BBC World News business headlines - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1057 </DOCNO> Ex-Nissan boss Ghosn leaves a Tokyo jail on bail - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1058 </DOCNO> Technology of Business news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1059 </DOCNO> Adobe Flash Player is finally laid to rest - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1060 </DOCNO> How does a museum remember a defeat? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1061 </DOCNO> Alexei Navalny: Russia's vociferous Putin critic - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1062 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Nisra records highest ever weekly deaths - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1063 </DOCNO> Wolves 2-3 West Brom: Sam Allardyce joy at 'big big victory' in Black Country derby - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1064 </DOCNO> In Pictures news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1065 </DOCNO> Indonesia earthquake: Woman rescued from rubble - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1066 </DOCNO> African news updates from the BBC - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1067 </DOCNO> CEO Secrets: 'Ask your investors for a yes or no' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1068 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Nursing Covid patients 'a harrowing experience' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1069 </DOCNO> The photographers capturing buildings and biscuits in 3D - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1070 </DOCNO> Business review of 2020: Covid-19 and Trump - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1071 </DOCNO> Students save on fees, but Chile's universities struggle - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1072 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Visiting suspended across NI hospitals - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1073 </DOCNO> Leeds United | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1074 </DOCNO> Africa's week in pictures: 8 - 14 January 2021 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1075 </DOCNO> Living with IBD: Ulcerative colitis and Crohn's disease - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1076 </DOCNO> Champions League: How well do you remember the 2019-20 tournament? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1077 </DOCNO> Boy arrives in UK after Uganda adoption battle - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1078 </DOCNO> Dating coach Sami Wunder reveals dilemma when starting out - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1079 </DOCNO> Robots to take on more supermarket tasks - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1080 </DOCNO> Beauty professionals hope for prettier picture in 2021 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1081 </DOCNO> West Ham United | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1082 </DOCNO> Pisa tests: UK rises in international school rankings - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1083 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Leaders hold 'positive' meeting with retail sector - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1084 </DOCNO> Your pictures on the theme of 'my hobby' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1085 </DOCNO> Covid in India: How do you vaccinate 1.3 billion people? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1086 </DOCNO> Volcanoes - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1087 </DOCNO> German chancellor race: The men vying for Merkel's job - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1088 </DOCNO> US backs down from tariffs over French tech giant taxes - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1089 </DOCNO> Hosts Cameroon open delayed CHAN with win over Zimbabwe - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1090 </DOCNO> Reaching 130 million girls with no access to school - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1091 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Negative test required for Ireland arrivals - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1092 </DOCNO> Your pictures of Scotland 1 - 8 January - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1093 </DOCNO> Football quiz: What can you remember about football in 2020? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1094 </DOCNO> How did the pilot survive this plane crash? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1095 </DOCNO> Staying one step ahead of the cyber-spies - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1096 </DOCNO> Covid: What are the new UK travel rules? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1097 </DOCNO> David Attenborough to front government-funded 5G AR app - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1098 </DOCNO> Istanbul Basaksehir 1-1 Sivasspor: Visitors play in all-white kit during snowstorm - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1099 </DOCNO> Ethiopia's Oromia conflict: Why a teacher was killed 'execution-style' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1100 </DOCNO> Pisa tests boss: Wales education system 'lost its soul' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1101 </DOCNO> AQE says bishop's statement 'highly defamatory' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1102 </DOCNO> Asia news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1103 </DOCNO> Building frozen castles at China's Harbin Ice Festival - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1104 </DOCNO> Will Gompertz | BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1105 </DOCNO> Manchester United: Bruno Fernandes says 'you don't want your rivals at the same level' - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1106 </DOCNO> How to become a professional shopper - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1107 </DOCNO> China's drinkers develop taste for home-grown wines - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1108 </DOCNO> Atlético Madrid | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1109 </DOCNO> Boris Johnson says girls' education key to ending poverty - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1110 </DOCNO> In pictures: The UK welcomes in the new year - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1111 </DOCNO> President Trump becomes first president to be impeached twice - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1112 </DOCNO> Tottenham Hotspur | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1113 </DOCNO> The search engine boss who wants to help us all plant trees - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1114 </DOCNO> Would you eat chicken grown in a lab? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1115 </DOCNO> Europe news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1116 </DOCNO> Latest Northern Ireland weather forecast - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1117 </DOCNO> Judges reject Lockerbie bomber's appeal against conviction - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1118 </DOCNO> Covid: 'Opportunity as well as threat' from pandemic tech advances - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1119 </DOCNO> Jadon Sancho: Have Manchester United missed chance to buy Borussia Dortmund star? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1120 </DOCNO> Week in pictures: 5 - 11 December 2020 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1121 </DOCNO> UK universities see boom in Chinese students - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1122 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Laptop donations a lifeline for mother-of-six - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1123 </DOCNO> Leicester 2-0 Southampton: Saints 'running out of players' - Hasenhuttl - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1124 </DOCNO> The man who sells 700 million sandwiches a year - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1125 </DOCNO> Asia news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1126 </DOCNO> Dutch Rutte government resigns over child welfare fraud scandal - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1127 </DOCNO> Are 'cryonic technicians' the key to immortality? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1128 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Businesses 'left in the dark' over support scheme - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1129 </DOCNO> CEO Secrets: The dads getting entrepreneurial in lockdown - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1130 </DOCNO> Sevilla | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1131 </DOCNO> England's Big Picture: 4 - 10 January - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1132 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Anger over US decision on foreign students' visas - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1133 </DOCNO> ‘Trump impeachment sets precedent against free speech’ - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1134 </DOCNO> Leicester 2-0 Southampton: Rodgers pleased with 'outstanding' second half - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1135 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: The stress of leading a start-up through the pandemic - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1136 </DOCNO> Taliban cracks down on 'costly' polygamy - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1137 </DOCNO> 'New York is not dead, but it is on life support' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1138 </DOCNO> Who wants to follow in Merkel's footsteps? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1139 </DOCNO> Wanted: Robot wrangler, no experience required - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1140 </DOCNO> African news updates from the BBC - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1141 </DOCNO> Aerial photos capture 'tree of life' structures in Norfolk and Suffolk - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1142 </DOCNO> Covid-19: St Mary’s and Charing Cross Hospital 10 months on - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1143 </DOCNO> Nóra Quoirin: 'Compelling evidence' of abduction - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1144 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Is Northern Ireland winning the battle against the virus? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1145 </DOCNO> The woman who wants everyone to get a pension - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1146 </DOCNO> Brexit: End to Gibraltar land border prompts joy and trepidation - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1147 </DOCNO> Amazon plots a course into the healthcare industry - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1148 </DOCNO> Colourising historical photos of the civil rights movement - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1149 </DOCNO> Why the humble text message is a key campaign tool - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1150 </DOCNO> Holstein Kiel 2-2 Bayern Munich (6-5 pens): Second tier side stun German Cup holders - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1151 </DOCNO> 'US far-right is furious over Trump impeachment' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1152 </DOCNO> Global Education news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1153 </DOCNO> January transfer window 2021: Who could be on the move? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1154 </DOCNO> Uganda elections 2021: Museveni takes lead as Bobi Wine cries foul - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1155 </DOCNO> 'People told me my plans for a skincare firm were crazy' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1156 </DOCNO> In pictures: Aurora Borealis lights up sky above Scotland - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1157 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: What’s it like to start a new job when working remotely? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1158 </DOCNO> Fifa Club World Cup: Auckland City withdraw because of Covid-19 rules in New Zealand - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1159 </DOCNO> Real Sociedad | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1160 </DOCNO> Tech trends in 2021: Fast planes and homeworking - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1161 </DOCNO> Trump: 'Violence and vandalism have no place in our country' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1162 </DOCNO> Crystal Palace | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1163 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Moy Park firms to introduce rapid testing - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1164 </DOCNO> Fashion - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1165 </DOCNO> Carly Fiorina's journey from secretary to CEO - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1166 </DOCNO> Week in pictures: 9-15 January 2021 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1167 </DOCNO> Dakar Rally: Pierre Cherpin - French rider dies after crash on stage seven - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1168 </DOCNO> Why Covid may mean more facial recognition tech - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1169 </DOCNO> What will be the big tech changes in 2021? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1170 </DOCNO> Burnley | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1171 </DOCNO> Covid-19: NI to introduce international travel Covid tests - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1172 </DOCNO> FC Santa Claus manager on running a football club in Lapland: 'I've never been so happy in my life' - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1173 </DOCNO> 'I might die because of surgery delays due to Covid' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1174 </DOCNO> UK internet use doubles in 2020 due to pandemic - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1175 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: British tourist blamed for Lauberhorn ski race cancellation - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1176 </DOCNO> Your pictures of Scotland 8 - 15 January - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1177 </DOCNO> India couple bullied for intimate wedding photoshoot - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1178 </DOCNO> Why shops are going over to the 'dark' side - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1179 </DOCNO> Madagascar: UN's WFP warns of a humanitarian crisis due to drought and Covid-19 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1180 </DOCNO> Ballyboley: Lorry driver may lose sight after bin attack - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1181 </DOCNO> Sri Lanka v England: Joe Root makes 168 not out as tourists build big lead - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1182 </DOCNO> CEO Secrets: 'Try bartering to kickstart your business' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1183 </DOCNO> Entertainers find new ways to pay the bills - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1184 </DOCNO> Why do women appear to bear the brunt of ageism at work? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1185 </DOCNO> Jaguar's 50-year old XJ model to be electric-powered - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1186 </DOCNO> Amad Diallo: Why Man Utd signing bears comparison with Cristiano Ronaldo transfer - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1187 </DOCNO> Hair salon seriously damaged by car crash - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1188 </DOCNO> Transfer rumours: Pogba, Rice, Wijnaldum, Garcia, Wilshere, Martinez, Neto - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1189 </DOCNO> Hailstorm turns city streets into raging rivers - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1190 </DOCNO> How her own illness led one woman to set up a global firm - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1191 </DOCNO> Quiz: Name the teams in the Champions League group stage - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1192 </DOCNO> EU must 'move at speed' on space broadband network - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1193 </DOCNO> Rajini Chandy: The 69-year-old Indian actress trolled for ‘too sexy’ photos - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1194 </DOCNO> CES 2021: Smart dog flaps, home robots and tech news - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1195 </DOCNO> In Pictures news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1196 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Eight times as many pupils in school this lockdown - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1197 </DOCNO> Premier League celebrations: Leicester & James Maddison lead the way - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1198 </DOCNO> Why ‘flight shame’ is making people swap planes for trains - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1199 </DOCNO> Autism: 'Shame and blame' in some BAME communities - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1200 </DOCNO> Eight things we learned about new businesses in lockdown - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1201 </DOCNO> Cowes Week set for 5G video from racing yachts trial - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1202 </DOCNO> Transgender people - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1203 </DOCNO> Will vitamin D really help me fight off Covid-19? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1204 </DOCNO> England's Big Picture: 11 - 17 January - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1205 </DOCNO> Fresh calls for NI mother and baby homes inquiry - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1206 </DOCNO> Fulham | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1207 </DOCNO> SLS: Nasa's crucial 'megarocket' test cut short - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1208 </DOCNO> David Moyes hails 'new West Ham' after 1-0 win over Burnley - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1209 </DOCNO> Gutted: Europe's fishing deal with the UK - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1210 </DOCNO> Islam Slimani: Striker leaves Leicester to join Lyon on free transfer - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1211 </DOCNO> Can supermarket security guards help with mask rules? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1212 </DOCNO> Simon Jack | BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1213 </DOCNO> Fulham 0-1 Chelsea: Lampard says lack of goals has affected confidence - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1214 </DOCNO> A photographer's secrets to capturing wildlife on Bardsey Island - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1215 </DOCNO> Climate change - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1216 </DOCNO> Does getting coronavirus make you immune? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1217 </DOCNO> NBA: Joel Embiid stars as Philadelphia 76ers beat Miami Heat; LeBron James guides LA Lakers to win - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1218 </DOCNO> What will be Covid-19's long-term global economic impact? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1219 </DOCNO> Billionaire UK beauty boss continues expansion with US deal - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1220 </DOCNO> Covid: India's coronavirus outbreak in 200 seconds - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1221 </DOCNO> Liverpool v Manchester United: Jurgen Klopp says 'I have no skills for mind games' - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1222 </DOCNO> Northern Ireland news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1223 </DOCNO> 'Everybody can join in a sea shanty' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1224 </DOCNO> Mesut Ozil: Arsenal midfielder close to Fenerbahce move - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1225 </DOCNO> United States - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1226 </DOCNO> Australia | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1227 </DOCNO> Basketball Scores - Latest scores from BBL and NBA - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1228 </DOCNO> The black-owned coffee firm that became a bestseller - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1229 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Lichfield Cathedral becomes a vaccination hub - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1230 </DOCNO> NBA: Los Angeles Lakers hope to meet President-elect Joe Biden but champions lose at Spurs - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1231 </DOCNO> rewind </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1232 </DOCNO> How your fridge is heating up the planet - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1233 </DOCNO> When driving a tuk-tuk pays more than making art - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1234 </DOCNO> Sheffield United: 'Pressure off' but can Blades produce a miracle after finally winning? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1235 </DOCNO> Aston Villa | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1236 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Your questions answered - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1237 </DOCNO> US Capitol on high alert ahead of Biden's inauguration - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1238 </DOCNO> The two students who took on Coke and Pepsi - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1239 </DOCNO> Irish mother and baby homes: Timeline of controversy - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1240 </DOCNO> Basketball Schedule - BBL schedule and NBA schedule - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1241 </DOCNO> Soutik Biswas | BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1242 </DOCNO> Arsenal | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1243 </DOCNO> CES 2021: 'Wearable tech that’s like using the Force’ - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1244 </DOCNO> Why are there so few black tech entrepreneurs? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1245 </DOCNO> Foyle walkway prompts Covid-19 social distancing concern - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1246 </DOCNO> Giannis Antetokounmpo: NBA star's rise from 'hustling' on Athens streets to MVP award - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1247 </DOCNO> Joe Biden - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1248 </DOCNO> NBA Standings - Basketball - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1249 </DOCNO> Connected World news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1250 </DOCNO> Sri Lanka v England: Michael Vaughan says hosts exposed tourists' weaknesses - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1251 </DOCNO> How China's giant solar farms are transforming world energy - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1252 </DOCNO> Liverpool v Man Utd: Jurgen Klopp's side have history of remarkable resilience - Danny Murphy analysis - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1253 </DOCNO> When local rivals meet in a cup - quiz - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1254 </DOCNO> 'Interns helped save my firm' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1255 </DOCNO> US politics - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1256 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Almost half of all cases in Ireland reported in last two weeks - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1257 </DOCNO> NBA: Kevin Durant and debutant James Harden star in Brooklyn Nets win - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1258 </DOCNO> David Beckham, LeBron James & Justin Bieber - Meet â€˜the GOATâ€™ of hat making - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1259 </DOCNO> Christianity - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1260 </DOCNO> Capitol riots: What are far-right Trump supporters saying? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1261 </DOCNO> England - Scores & Fixtures - Cricket - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1262 </DOCNO> Will Santa have enough bikes for Christmas Day? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1263 </DOCNO> Women's Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1264 </DOCNO> Brexit: The DUP's bruising battle for control - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1265 </DOCNO> India coronavirus: The mums who became pandemic chefs - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1266 </DOCNO> The Iranian immigrant who conquered online video tech - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1267 </DOCNO> Uganda elections 2021: 'We want peace' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1268 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Dealing with excessive facial hair during lockdown - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1269 </DOCNO> England Table - Cricket - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1270 </DOCNO> NYSE does a U-turn on Chinese telecoms delistings - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1271 </DOCNO> Chelsea | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1272 </DOCNO> How the Soviet Union's end sparked a grand rewilding - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1273 </DOCNO> Leagues & Cups - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1274 </DOCNO> Caoimhin Cassidy-Crossan: The Boy In The Burning Car - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1275 </DOCNO> Islamic veils - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1276 </DOCNO> "There is a mental health crisis with or without corona" - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1277 </DOCNO> The gaming boss who can't put the games down - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1278 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Belfast doctor warns oxygen supplies under 'extreme pressure' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1279 </DOCNO> Coronavirus and teachers: The forgotten school key workers - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1280 </DOCNO> NBA: Houston Rockets beat San Antonio Spurs - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1281 </DOCNO> Sheffield United | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1282 </DOCNO> England men's squad - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1283 </DOCNO> Chelsea v Man Utd: Could Sunday's WSL showdown prove to be the title decider? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1284 </DOCNO> Belgium after Brexit: How the change will affect popular exports - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1285 </DOCNO> Far-right online: 'I got them back on social media' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1286 </DOCNO> Philippines: Anti-'drug war' priest charged with sedition - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1287 </DOCNO> How Iceland is undoing carbon emissions for good - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1288 </DOCNO> Manchester City | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1289 </DOCNO> Religion - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1290 </DOCNO> Covid vaccine: Gwynedd pharmacy first to offer jab - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1291 </DOCNO> Trinity Rodman: NBA legend Dennis Rodman's daughter drafted second in NWSL - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1292 </DOCNO> 'We switched to virtual wine tastings during lockdown' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1293 </DOCNO> Teams - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1294 </DOCNO> Mother and baby homes: Call for Church of Ireland apology - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1295 </DOCNO> Revenge of the secretaries: The protest movement that inspired the film 9 to 5 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1296 </DOCNO> Covid-19: Hereford college A-level students on remote learning - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1297 </DOCNO> The awkward questions about slavery from tourists in US South - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1298 </DOCNO> How shrubs can help solve climate change - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1299 </DOCNO> 'I was heartbroken, I never thought I would find someone like her' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1300 </DOCNO> Four protests that triggered change - and one that didn't - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1301 </DOCNO> Donald Trump - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1302 </DOCNO> Quiz: Can you name the Premier League's most expensive January buys? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1303 </DOCNO> Kenya Covid-19: Has the pandemic led to an increase in FGM? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1304 </DOCNO> The Syrian mercenaries used as 'cannon fodder' in Nagorno-Karabakh - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1305 </DOCNO> US race relations - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1306 </DOCNO> LaMelo Ball: Charlotte Hornets rookie becomes youngest player in NBA history to score triple-double - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1307 </DOCNO> Christmas celebrations to go ahead in Bethlehem - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1308 </DOCNO> Brazil's Amazon: Deforestation 'surges to 12-year high' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1309 </DOCNO> 'My first collection failed, it was heartbreaking' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1310 </DOCNO> eBay - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1311 </DOCNO> Belfast Multi-Cultural Association building badly damaged by fire - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1312 </DOCNO> ‘I was in prison at 20 - and a music executive by 28’ - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1313 </DOCNO> Human rights - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1314 </DOCNO> Curator explains importance of American Civil War's black soldiers - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1315 </DOCNO> CEO Secrets: 'I sell smoked salmon on top of my day job' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1316 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: 'When coffins lined the streets of my hometown' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1317 </DOCNO> CEO Secrets: The graduates launching start-ups in lockdown - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1318 </DOCNO> Quiz: Can you name the starting XIs from the last time Man Utd won at Anfield? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1319 </DOCNO> 'Being sectioned felt like a punishment' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1320 </DOCNO> NBA: LA Lakers and LA Clippers win, Boston Celtics v Miami Heat called off - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1321 </DOCNO> The rise of India’s viral wedding photoshoots - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1322 </DOCNO> Why did the council 'house' me in a tent? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1323 </DOCNO> Australia v India: Shardul Thakur and Washington Sundar lead fightback in Brisbane - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1324 </DOCNO> Iran - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1325 </DOCNO> The bold plan to save Africa's largest forest - BBC Future </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1326 </DOCNO> Manchester United | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1327 </DOCNO> Bang Bang: The artist whoâ€™s tattooed LeBron James, Rihanna, Lewis Hamilton and Thierry Henry - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1328 </DOCNO> Unicef - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1329 </DOCNO> The beer brand putting India on the brewing map - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1330 </DOCNO> India | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1331 </DOCNO> What are the rules for commenting and uploading? - Using the BBC </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1332 </DOCNO> CEO Secrets: Older women strike out in lockdown - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1333 </DOCNO> SLS: Nasa's 'megarocket' engine test ends early - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1334 </DOCNO> The Lilium Jet makes a vertical take-off - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1335 </DOCNO> Tao Geoghegan Hart: The 'overnight sensation' 10 years in the making - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1336 </DOCNO> Sexism - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1337 </DOCNO> NBA: LA Lakers edge win over Chicago Bulls, Warriors beat Clippers - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1338 </DOCNO> Transfer rumours: Pogba, Rice, Wijnaldum, Garcia, Wilshere, Martinez, Neto - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1339 </DOCNO> Ireland | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1340 </DOCNO> New aircraft spy opportunities amid aerospace woes - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1341 </DOCNO> Jonathan Amos | BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1342 </DOCNO> Mars - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1343 </DOCNO> NBA Draft 2020: Could Anthony Edwards be the next LeBron James? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1344 </DOCNO> Nick Butter: The man who ran a marathon in every country in the world - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1345 </DOCNO> Everton | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1346 </DOCNO> 'It kind of makes debt cool – and it's not' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1347 </DOCNO> Pop music - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1348 </DOCNO> The explosive problem of 'zombie' batteries - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1349 </DOCNO> Pakistan - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1350 </DOCNO> Entrepreneurship news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1351 </DOCNO> CEO Secrets: 'Try bartering to kickstart your business' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1352 </DOCNO> LeBron James: I don't live my life thinking about legacy - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1353 </DOCNO> The Moon - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1354 </DOCNO> The Belgian 'hero' who invaded UK fishing waters - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1355 </DOCNO> Wolverhampton Wanderers | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1356 </DOCNO> Evangelical leader Franklin Graham: Trump is 'work in progress' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1357 </DOCNO> Wonder Woman 1984: Actress Lilly Aspell reveals how a chance encounter led her to the role - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1358 </DOCNO> The woman who quit smoking and built a global hypnotherapy firm - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1359 </DOCNO> Plastic surgery: Surgeons who target black women and use influencers for promotion - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1360 </DOCNO> Artemis - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1361 </DOCNO> 'Mythical' Aston Martin Bulldog supercar being restored - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1362 </DOCNO> Long Reads - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1363 </DOCNO> James Harden: Houston Rockets star joins Brooklyn Nets in three-team deal - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1364 </DOCNO> The airman from Sierra Leone who was shot down over Nazi Germany - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1365 </DOCNO> Ridley Scott inspires Network Rail’s cave-exploring drone - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1366 </DOCNO> 'Fear is the only thing that stops you. I had to give it a try’ - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1367 </DOCNO> Turning Paris's underground car parks into mushrooms farms - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1368 </DOCNO> Boeing - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1369 </DOCNO> January transfer window: Negotiator's guide to getting a deal done - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1370 </DOCNO> Asia - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1371 </DOCNO> How the satnav became a million dollar idea - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1372 </DOCNO> Nicaraguan zoo shows off white tiger cub Nieves - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1373 </DOCNO> Coronavirus in Wuhan: The son who lost his father to Covid-19 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1374 </DOCNO> The guy designing sneakers for NBA stars... and Cristiano Ronaldo - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1375 </DOCNO> Lisa Montgomery: Looking for answers in the life of a killer - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1376 </DOCNO> Detectives and noxious locks take on bike thieves - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1377 </DOCNO> 'My chronic acne inspired me to start my own skincare company' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1378 </DOCNO> Newcastle United | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1379 </DOCNO> Ageism - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1380 </DOCNO> Young, black and more likely to die in Brazil - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1381 </DOCNO> How tech can just about save Christmas Day - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1382 </DOCNO> Covid-19 North East: 300 days since first lockdown - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1383 </DOCNO> Exploration of Mars - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1384 </DOCNO> Country music - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1385 </DOCNO> Nasa - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1386 </DOCNO> Dating coach Sami Wunder: 'Charge the full market rate' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1387 </DOCNO> NBA: Minnesota Timberwolves' Karl-Anthony Towns defiant over Covid-19 - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1388 </DOCNO> Rory Cellan-Jones | BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1389 </DOCNO> Liverpool v Manchester United - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1390 </DOCNO> Nepal - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1391 </DOCNO> USA v Iran: The historic 2000 friendly match planned to bring countries together - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1392 </DOCNO> A palm oil alternative could help save rainforests - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1393 </DOCNO> CEO Secrets: 'I couldn't build a company on my own' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1394 </DOCNO> Olivia Rodrigo celebrates going to number one - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1395 </DOCNO> Human spaceflight - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1396 </DOCNO> In pictures: Troops guard US Capitol, one week after riots - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1397 </DOCNO> Sign language: Seven-year-old teaching classmates - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1398 </DOCNO> Black Lives Matter protest: Why was Churchill's statue defaced? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1399 </DOCNO> How much can Joe Biden get done on the US economy? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1400 </DOCNO> Tech Tent: Will better batteries persuade us to go electric? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1401 </DOCNO> Week in pictures: 2 - 8 January 2021 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1402 </DOCNO> In pictures: Storm Filomena hits Spain as Greeks bask in heatwave - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1403 </DOCNO> Wands revive memories of the smart home dream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1404 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Lessons from 2008 for the class of 2020 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1405 </DOCNO> Championship - Football - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1406 </DOCNO> Man rescued from submerged vehicle in Peru - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1407 </DOCNO> So you want a career in computer games tournaments? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1408 </DOCNO> Photographs of two families found on one 20-year-old film - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1409 </DOCNO> BBC Monitoring - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1410 </DOCNO> NBA: James Harden reported to be joining Brooklyn Nets as they beat New York Knicks - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1411 </DOCNO> Exploration of the Moon - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1412 </DOCNO> Human rights in China - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1413 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: PM says UK 'taking steps' over Brazil variant - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1414 </DOCNO> BBC Trending | BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1415 </DOCNO> How Ebola prepared one doctor for Covid-19 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1416 </DOCNO> Netflix founder: 'Learn when to get out of the way' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1417 </DOCNO> Long Reads news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1418 </DOCNO> Economy news stream - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1419 </DOCNO> A supermarket is being piloted which has no tills - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1420 </DOCNO> Minnesota - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1421 </DOCNO> Sheffield United v Tottenham Hotspur - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1422 </DOCNO> Wales Covid-19 Evidence Centre to 'shape' response to pandemic - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1423 </DOCNO> Leicester City | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1424 </DOCNO> BBL Cup: Newcastle Eagles beat Leicester Riders to join London Lions in final - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1425 </DOCNO> Conspiracy theories - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1426 </DOCNO> Edward Colston - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1427 </DOCNO> Muslims - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1428 </DOCNO> Brighton & Hove Albion | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1429 </DOCNO> Argentina abortion: Activists celebrate Senate vote - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1430 </DOCNO> Jimmy Carter: The story behind the Premier League's first British Asian player - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1431 </DOCNO> Liverpool | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1432 </DOCNO> Mountaineering - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1433 </DOCNO> US election 2020: How to spot disinformation - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1434 </DOCNO> Jeremy Hunt's son asks Tony Blair if 'world is going to end' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1435 </DOCNO> Renee Montgomery: The basketball star partially responsible for Raphael Warnock's Senate success - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1436 </DOCNO> Coronavirus lockdown measures - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1437 </DOCNO> LeBron James is on basketball's Mount Rushmore, says Ovie Soko - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1438 </DOCNO> 'I was standing at the wrong end of a machine gun' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1439 </DOCNO> Racism - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1440 </DOCNO> Living through lockdown when the love of your life is in a care home - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1441 </DOCNO> The Burundian refugee soap maker who is fighting coronavirus in Kenya - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1442 </DOCNO> Overnight snow fall causes travel difficulties in Scotland - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1443 </DOCNO> Robert Jenrick - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1444 </DOCNO> Emma Hayes column: Why we are all responsible for women's game - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1445 </DOCNO> Winstone and Redman support Bravo 22 Company theatre project - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1446 </DOCNO> Beirut explosion: The architect rebuilding families' homes for free - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1447 </DOCNO> Covid in Scotland: Stricter retail and takeaway rules 'to cut contact' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1448 </DOCNO> North Carolina - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1449 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Does your mask need an upgrade? - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1450 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: 'New Zealand will get rid of the virus again' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1451 </DOCNO> CES 2021: Smart pillows and internet-connected smoothies - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1452 </DOCNO> Liverpool v Man Utd: Who made your combined XI? - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1453 </DOCNO> Captagon: Destroying the frontline drug - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1454 </DOCNO> Southampton | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1455 </DOCNO> Facebook - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1456 </DOCNO> Yoweri Museveni - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1457 </DOCNO> Meet India's lower-caste Hindu priest - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1458 </DOCNO> Samsung S21 Ultra: First look at the new device - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1459 </DOCNO> Uighurs - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1460 </DOCNO> Companies - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1461 </DOCNO> 'I wanted to paint people who looked like me' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1462 </DOCNO> Johan 'N0tail' Sundstein: Inside the world's richest e-sports player's mansion - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1463 </DOCNO> Juventus v Sassuolo: The Serie A minnows with Champions League ambition - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1464 </DOCNO> Branwen Jeffreys | BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1465 </DOCNO> 2020 and me: 'I know the value of family more' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1466 </DOCNO> Teen detained over 180mph stolen motorbike pursuit - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1467 </DOCNO> Music - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1468 </DOCNO> Lucas Piazon: Chelsea's longest-serving player finally departs Stamford Bridge permanently - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1469 </DOCNO> Richard Leonard: 'Leadership speculation was harming Labour' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1470 </DOCNO> Using tech to prevent car theft in Cameroon - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1471 </DOCNO> Dow Jones Industrial Average - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1472 </DOCNO> Leeds 0-1 Brighton: Marcelo Bielsa - Performances cause me worry - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1473 </DOCNO> Disinformation - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1474 </DOCNO> Matt McGrath | BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1475 </DOCNO> Fulham 0-1 Chelsea: Scott Parker says Antonee Robinson's red card 'changed the game' - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1476 </DOCNO> Social media - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1477 </DOCNO> 'Making pizzas used to be a hobby, now it's my business' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1478 </DOCNO> Sri Lanka v England - Cricket - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1479 </DOCNO> Global Happiness Conference comes to school in Bewdley - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1480 </DOCNO> Indonesia - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1481 </DOCNO> Uganda - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1482 </DOCNO> Dog walkers in Oregon caught in tidal surge - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1483 </DOCNO> Impeachment of Donald Trump - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1484 </DOCNO> Transfer news: Done deals during January 2021 - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1485 </DOCNO> Bobi Wine - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1486 </DOCNO> Scottish Premiership | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1487 </DOCNO> The secret artists creating miniature buildings for street mice - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1488 </DOCNO> Electric cars dominate at the Geneva Motor Show - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1489 </DOCNO> Sri Lanka v England LIVE, first Test day four, Galle - score, commentary & updates - Live - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1490 </DOCNO> Sean Coughlan | BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1491 </DOCNO> 2020 through the lens of a photojournalist - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1492 </DOCNO> Afghanistan - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1493 </DOCNO> Storm Filomena: Heavy snowfall closes roads in Madrid - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1494 </DOCNO> Premier League predictions: Lawro v You Me At Six drummer & Man Utd fan Dan Flint - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1495 </DOCNO> Capitol riots: 'It was life or death' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1496 </DOCNO> Sri Lanka v England LIVE, first Test day four, Galle - score, commentary & updates - Live - BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1497 </DOCNO> CEO Secrets: 'I wish I'd planned for my success' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1498 </DOCNO> See the snow-topped Brecon Beacons from home during lockdown - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1499 </DOCNO> Xinjiang - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1500 </DOCNO> Adobe Flash Player reaches the end of its life - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1501 </DOCNO> Indonesia: Thousands flee after volcano erupts - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1502 </DOCNO> LGBT - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1503 </DOCNO> The challenge of doing business in Argentina - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1504 </DOCNO> A-level and GCSE tests: 'We have unfair chances this year at exams' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1505 </DOCNO> Covid vaccination: A 'bittersweet' moment for India's health workers - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1506 </DOCNO> Rutte: Dutch cabinet decision to resign 'unavoidable' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1507 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: People with learning disabilities 'at risk of falling through cracks' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1508 </DOCNO> Gibraltar UK deal with Spain 'a boost for economy' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1509 </DOCNO> New Zealand | BBC Sport </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1510 </DOCNO> S&P 500 - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1511 </DOCNO> Miniature heart inventor: Breakthroughs take time to sell - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1512 </DOCNO> The plane that can fly 600 miles on batteries alone - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1513 </DOCNO> Caravans making a comeback - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1514 </DOCNO> 'Promoting junior staff to directors saved my firm' - BBC News </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1515 </DOCNO> null </DOC>